<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<policy>
	<segment>
		<title tagname="h2" depth="1" font-size="2.12" font-weight="1.0" category="">Khan Academy Privacy Principles</title>
		<segment>
			<title tagname="h3" depth="1" font-size="1.25" font-weight="1.75" category="">
				Our Privacy Policy is fueled by our commitment to these Privacy Principles:
				</title>
			<item>We’re deeply committed to creating a safe and secure online environment for you.</item>
		<item>We do not sell your personal information to third parties. We established Khan Academy as a nonprofit organization so that our mission of education and your trust will not be in conflict with a for-profit motive.</item>
		<item>We strive to provide you with access to and control over the information you give us, and we take the protection of your information very seriously.</item>
		<item>We take extra precautions for our younger learners as described in our Children’s Privacy Notice, including restricting child accounts to automatically block features that would allow a child to post or disclose personal information.</item>
		<item>We do not display advertising on Khan Academy. Our mission is to provide you with a world class education, not to sell you products.</item>
</segment>
	</segment>
	<segment>
		<title tagname="h2" depth="1" font-size="2.12" font-weight="1.0" category="">
			Overview
			</title>
		<segment>
			<title tagname="h3" depth="1" font-size="1.25" font-weight="1.75" category="15;15">
				Use by Children and Students
				</title>
			<paragraph category="15;15">For specific information about how we collect, use, and process personal information when providing the Service to schools, school districts, and teachers, please review the School and Student Use.</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="15;15">Our Children’s Privacy Notice describes how we collect, use, and process personal information from children under 13.</paragraph>
</segment>
		<paragraph category="">Khan Academy, Inc. (“Khan Academy”, “our”, “us”, or “we”) is a US-based charitable nonprofit organization. As a 501(c)(3) nonprofit, we use the information we collect to provide you with a better experience and fulfill our mission of providing a free, world-class education for anyone, anywhere. We established ourselves as a nonprofit organization so that a for-profit motive will not interfere with our mission of providing a trusted educational resource.</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="">We are committed to protecting your privacy. We understand how important privacy is to you, and we are committed to protecting your privacy and to creating a safe and secure environment for learners of all ages. This Privacy Policy explains how information is collected, used, shared, and protected by Khan Academy when you use (or access) our website at www.khanacademy.org, our mobile application, and online service (collectively, our “Service”). Our Khan Academy Kids mobile application is governed by a different privacy policy.</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="">Note: For each section in this Privacy Policy, you can view the general privacy practices at the beginning of the section, and see more information by reviewing “Learn More” for the relevant section.</paragraph>
</segment>
	<segment>
		<title tagname="h2" depth="1" font-size="2.12" font-weight="1.0" category="8,9;8,9">
			Collection of information
			</title>
		<paragraph category="8,9.1,9.2,9.3;8,9.1,9.2,9.3">We collect information in the following ways, depending on your use of the Service and your account settings:</paragraph>
		<item>We collect information from you directly, such as when you create an account, communicate with us, participate in activities, events or surveys, or otherwise provide information during your use of the Service.</item>
		<item>We may collect information from others, such as your parent, teacher, or School, or third parties (meaning organizations outside of Khan Academy), such as third party applications that you use to connect to the Service.</item>
		<item>We collect some information automatically, such as information about your use of the Service and the devices you use to access the Service. We may use cookies, web beacons, and similar technologies to collect information as explained in our Cookie Notice.</item>
		<paragraph category="8,9;8,9">Examples of information we may collect includes:</paragraph>
		<item>Account registration information (username, birthdate, and email)</item>
		<item>Information about your browser or device, and general location</item>
		<item>Information you choose to include in your profile or post in public areas of the Service</item>
		<item>Information you may provide in connection with specific features or special programs</item>
		<item>Non-personal information which may be linked to your personal information, including Information about your use of our Service</item>
		<paragraph category="8,9,15;8,9,15">Additional information about our collection of Child and student data is provided in our Children’s Privacy Notice and Schools and Student Use. Further information about how Khan Academy collects your information is provided under “Learn More”.</paragraph>
		<item>Contact and profile information. When you create an account on the Khan Academy Service we may collect information including your name, email address, and birthdate (for compliance purposes). We also collect sign-in information including username and password. After you register, you may also choose to provide additional information in your profile, such as your nickname, and other personal or demographic information.</item>
		<item>Your communications with us. We may collect information from you at other times, such as when you request customer support, send us an email, post a comment, complete a user survey, participate in a special program, or otherwise communicate with Khan Academy (including via third party services).</item>
		<item>Information obtained from a school, or from other users. We make available certain features on our Service that allow other users to provide us information about you. For example, a school or teacher may provide information relating to participants in a class, or a parent may provide information relating to a Child User, such as when a parent registers an account for their Child and provide us with certain information about the Child, such as user name and age. Please review our Children’s Privacy Notice and Schools and Student Use for additional information about use of our Service by Children and students.</item>
		<item>Information from Single Sign On (SSO) authentication services. If you decide to register for an account (or access your account) through an authentication service (such as Google Accounts or Clever as a Single Sign On, also known as a SSO) (“Authentication Service”), we may collect information from these third-party services, consistent with your privacy settings in your account with the relevant Authentication Service.</item>
		<item>Social media sharing. You may choose to directly share a link to the content you are viewing on Khan Academy by clicking on a third party application icon (such as choosing to share a link via your social media account like Twitter or Facebook). It is your choice whether to log-in to your social media account, so that you can post a direct link to the content you are viewing. Use of social media sharing is optional.</item>
		<item>Information we collect to enable your participation in special programs or features. Khan Academy may feature a special program or activity we offer in partnership with a third party. If you participate in these special programs, Khan Academy may collect information from you to facilitate those programs. For example, LearnStorm participants may be asked to provide information related to event logistics and prize awarding and processing (e.g., contact information, dietary restrictions, shirt sizes, etc.). In connection with official test practice services such as our Official SAT Practice service, we may obtain information about your test scores from the test administrator (e.g., College Board) if you enable certain features.</item>
		<item>Information provided by partners and other sources. We may also receive information from third party organizations with which we partner to provide educational services. If we associate information from other sources with personal information that we collect through our Service, we will treat the combined information as personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.</item>
		<item>Information about your use of our Service.We may collect usage information about your use of our Service, such as the number of problems you have attempted, the number of videos you have viewed, and the amount of time spent to complete a problem. This enables us to better tailor educational experiences that are most appropriate for you.</item>
		<item>Location information. We may collect and use information about your location (such as your country) or infer your approximate location based on your IP address in order to provide you with tailored educational experiences for your region, but we don’t collect the precise geolocation of you or your device. You may be able to change the settings on your computer or mobile device to prevent it from providing us with any location information.</item>
		<item>Usage and device information. To provide a personalized learning and high-quality experience for our users, we may use various technologies that automatically record certain technical information from your browser or device when you visit our website, read our emails, use our Service or otherwise engage with us (e.g., the model of the laptop or mobile device and operating system version you use). You can learn more about our use of these technologies (and how to manage their use) in our Cookie Notice.</item>
</segment>
	<segment>
		<title tagname="h2" depth="1" font-size="2.12" font-weight="1.0" category="11;11">
			Use of information
			</title>
		<paragraph category="11;11">Khan Academy uses information collected for the purposes of:</paragraph>
		<item>providing the Service</item>
		<item>personalizing your experience</item>
		<item>communicating with you about your account and our Service (including responding to inquiries and sharing information about new features and offerings that may be of interest)</item>
		<item>enabling your participation in special programs that we may offer in partnerships with third parties (if you choose to participate in such special programs)</item>
		<item>understanding and improving our Service, and developing new or improved educational offerings</item>
		<paragraph category="11;11">We may also use de-identified or aggregated information for product development, research, analytics and other purposes, including for the purpose of analyzing, improving or marketing our Service, for demonstrating the impact of our Service, or conducting educational research.</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="4.1,11;4.1,11">Khan Academy uses your information in the following ways:</paragraph>
		<item>To provide our Service. Khan Academy uses your information to operate, maintain, and provide all of the features of our Service.</item>
		<item>To personalize your experience. We use your information to personalize your experience while using the Service, including on various devices you may use to access the Service. For instance, Khan Academy remembers your recent activity so we can recommend the most appropriate content for you on your next visit and provide personalized learning experiences.</item>
		<item>To communicate with you. We use your information to communicate with you about your account and respond to inquiries. We may also use your information to provide you with information about Khan Academy’s features, services and other offerings that may be of interest to you, and communicate with you about our philanthropic mission and fundraising for our mission.</item>
		<item>To enable your participation in Khan Academy partnership arrangements. We use your information to enable your participation in programs or features we may offer in partnership with third parties, to the extent you decide to participate in such programs.</item>
		<item>To understand, improve, and develop our Service. Khan Academy uses information to understand and analyze the usage trends, learning behaviors, and preferences of our users, to improve the way the Service works and looks, and to create new features and functionality.</item>
		<item>To develop new educational offerings. We may use information to maintain, develop, support and improve our Service and other educational products and services, and for educational research.</item>
		<item>For legal, compliance or safety reasons. We may use or share information to comply with applicable laws, rules, or regulations, and our Terms of Service, including protecting the safety and rights of Khan Academy, users, and the general public.</item>
		<paragraph category="11;11">For information regarding processing of personal information relevant for international visitors outside of the United States, please review Regional Information.</paragraph>
</segment>
	<segment>
		<title tagname="h2" depth="1" font-size="2.12" font-weight="1.0" category="17;17">
			Sharing and disclosure of information
			</title>
		<paragraph category="17;17">Khan Academy takes great care to protect the personal information you provide to us. We do not sell your personal information to third parties. This section explains circumstances in which we may share personal information with third parties.</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="17.1,17.2;17.1,17.2">We may share personal information:</paragraph>
		<item>with other users of our Service, if you use features that enable you to share your information with (or make it accessible to) others.</item>
		<item>with Vendors, consultants and other service providers working on our behalf</item>
		<item>with other users that are associated with your account, such as a parent, teacher or coach.</item>
		<item>with your school, if you are using our Service for school purposes (please see Schools and Student Use for more information).</item>
		<item>with your consent (including third party applications that you choose to use, such as complementary services or an Authentication Service). If you choose to use a third-party application or service, the use of your information by the third party will be governed by that party’s privacy policy.</item>
		<item>in connection with business transfers (due to mergers and acquisitions).</item>
		<item>for compliance purposes, such as when reasonably necessary to protect the security and safety of our users or Service, or when permitted by law.</item>
		<paragraph category="17.2;17.2">We may also share de-identified or aggregated information that does not reasonably identify any individual.</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="17.2;17.2">Khan Academy may share or transfer your information in the following ways:</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="17.2;17.2">Certain features and functions of the Service may share your information with or make it accessible to others. For example, your information may be visible to others in the following circumstances:</paragraph>
		<item>Information you post to public spaces of the Service.When you post a question or answer to the Service, your profile, which could include your name and short biography, as well as the content of your posted comment, is visible to others on the Service. As with most online services, once your information is available to others online, it may be collected and used by the recipients or any other website visitor without restriction. As with online safety in general, consider which personal information (if any) you want to share in your profile or posts. We strongly advise that you do not use your real name (or other information that could be used to identify you) when creating your username (or profile).</item>
		<item>Information shared when your account is connected to another user account. When your account is connected to a teacher or coach, or your parent, that person will be able to see your profile information and your learning activity on the Service, such as which videos you have watched, the questions and responses you post, and other usage information. This information may include your name (not only your username) as well as information in your account profile and your account settings.</item>
		<paragraph category="17.1,17.2;17.1,17.2">You may provide consent or authorization to share your information with third party applications or services in several ways. Please note that these third parties are not governed by Khan Academy or the terms of this Privacy Policy. We recommend you review the privacy policy of any third party application or service before authorizing its access to your Khan Academy account information.</paragraph>
		<item>We may share information with third-party applications that you authorize. Third-party application developers and service providers may build complementary services for our platform, such as a mobile application for blind or low-vision learners. They may also use our Khan Academy content to build unaffiliated applications and services. If you connect your Khan Academy account to a third-party application or service, or approve access to your Khan Academy account by a third party, you consent to Khan Academy sharing your information with that third party.</item>
		<item>We may share information with third-party Single Sign On tools that you choose. Khan Academy provides you with opportunities to register an account with (and/or sign on to) Khan Academy by using a Single Sign On Authentication Service. If you choose to use the Authentication Service, these third-party services may be able to collect or infer information about you, including information about your use of our Service (i.e, your log-in activity), in accordance with their own privacy policies.</item>
		<item>We may share information with social networks at your request.You may choose to share Khan Academy content with others by email (or by posting to social media sites) through third party integrations with social media sites (like Facebook or Twitter). These third parties may use your information as described in their own privacy policies. Use of this feature is optional.</item>
		<item>We may share information in connection with special programs you participate in. If you participate in special programs where Khan Academy partners with third parties, Khan Academy may share information collected from or about you with its third-party partners to facilitate the program or services being offered. For instance, if you participate in Khan Academy’s SAT practice offering, Khan Academy and College Board may share information regarding your practice activity, tests taken, and test scores relating to that program. These partners may use your information as described in their own privacy policies.</item>
		<item>We may share information with your consent. Khan Academy does not share your information with third-party organizations for their marketing or promotional use without your consent. In some instances, you may be able to grant us permission to share your information with authorized partners, nonprofit organizations, and other entities that are not affiliated with Khan Academy. In these cases, we will only provide to these third parties the information you have authorized or asked us to share.</item>
		<paragraph category="17.1;17.1">If you are a School User or teacher, Khan Academy may share certain information with your School. For more information, please review the section entitled Schools and Student Use.</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="17.2;17.2">In certain circumstances, Khan Academy may share de-identified or aggregated information that does not reasonably identify you as an individual for various purposes. For example, we may share de-identified information with business partners to improve our Service or offerings or to conduct educational research. If we disclose information to third parties for research or product development purposes, such information will be aggregated and/or de-identified to reasonably avoid identification of specific individuals.</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="17.1,17.2;17.1,17.2">In order to provide our Service, Khan Academy may share information with our employees and trusted vendors, third party service providers or other individuals, such as entities providing billing, customer support, analytics, hosting, marketing and similar services. When we share information with third party service providers or vendors, these third parties are contractually obligated to maintain the security and confidentiality of that information.</paragraph>
		<item>We may share information in the context of a change of business, including a merger or acquisition.In the event that Khan Academy is involved in a merger, acquisition, bankruptcy, change of control, or any form of sale of some or all of our assets, your information may be transferred or disclosed in connection with such business transaction. If the transaction involves the transfer of Student Personal Data to a third party, we will require the new owner to continue to honor the terms provided in this Privacy Policy, or we will provide the School with notice and an opportunity to opt-out of the transfer of Student Personal Data by deleting Student Personal Data before the transfer occurs.</item>
		<item>Other instances. Khan Academy may share or disclose information if we have a good faith belief that doing so is reasonably necessary to: (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process, or enforceable governmental request; (b) enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations thereof; (c) investigate or defend ourselves against any third-party claims or allegations; (d) detect, prevent or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues; (e) protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Khan Academy, our users, or the public; or (f) as otherwise required or permitted by law.</item>
</segment>
	<segment>
		<title tagname="h2" depth="1" font-size="2.12" font-weight="1.0" category="19;19">
			Sponsorship and Advertising
			</title>
		<paragraph category="19;19">As a nonprofit organization, Khan Academy relies on our sponsors, donors, and other contributors to provide funding necessary to provide the free Service to our users. From time to time, we permit third parties to sponsor content displayed on our Service.</paragraph>
		<item>For example, for-profit organizations may wish to sponsor all content related to a particular educational topic, such as astronomy or biology.</item>
		<item>Sponsored content will always be labeled (e.g., “Sponsored by ___”).</item>
		<item>Khan Academy does not share any of your personal information with these sponsors without your consent. We do not provide these sponsors with the ability to track or collect information about our site visitors or users.</item>
		<paragraph category="19;19">Khan Academy does not display third party advertisements on our Service. We may, from time to time, incorporate content or link to content provided by third parties that may be of interest to you and relevant to the educational context of our Service. Some of these materials or websites may include branding or advertisements as permitted by the third party owner or operator. For more information, please review Links to third parties.</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="15;15">Please note that we use our best efforts and take multiple steps to avoid the collection of information for targeted advertising purposes when we believe the Service is being used by Students or Children.</paragraph>
		<item>For example, we take steps to inhibit third party advertising networks from collecting information for targeted advertising purposes on webpages with child-directed content or when a Student or Child User logs into the Service.</item>
		<item>Khan Academy uses the available privacy functionality in YouTube to display video content on YouTube (see additional information under “Learn More”).</item>
		<paragraph category="15;15">Please review our Children’s Privacy Notice for more information.</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="15;15">We have turned on “Privacy-Enhanced Mode” for YouTube videos displayed on the Service. This means that YouTube does not place cookies or track viewing behavior for advertising purposes. Our student-facing content does not embed any YouTube videos that are not part of our content. We disabled certain functionality on YouTube (called “rel” functionality), so that content outside of our content is not played. We also use Google’s “child-directed treatment” tags to alert Google that our YouTube videos may be viewed by children or students. For more information, please see Google’s privacy practices.</paragraph>
</segment>
	<segment>
		<title tagname="h2" depth="1" font-size="2.12" font-weight="1.0" category="6;6">
			Transparency and your choice
			</title>
		<paragraph category="4,6;4,6">We take privacy very seriously. We strive to put you in control of the choices and decisions regarding your personal information.</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="4.2,6;4.2,6">We understand that your personal information is important to you, and that is why you have choices in how your personal information is used and shared. We want you to have access to your personal information, so that you can help keep it as accurate as possible.</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="4.3,6;4.3,6">For example, you can choose whether to create an account (or use the Service without registering). If you register for an account, you can:</paragraph>
		<item>Limit optional information you provide</item>
		<item>Choose whether you wish to share personal information with (and use) third party services</item>
		<item>Choose whether to add a coach to your account</item>
		<item>Choose whether you wish to receive optional email</item>
		<item>Update, correct, and delete your account information through your account settings</item>
		<paragraph category="4.3,4.9;4.3,4.9">In some cases, administrative controls for accounts used in a school setting, including the ability to modify or delete the account, are held by the school. For more information, please review our Children’s Privacy Notice and Schools and Student Use.</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="4.2,11;4.2,11">You can access most of our online resources without providing personal information. If you do not create an account, however, Khan Academy will not be able to provide you with certain features and functionalities found on our Service. You can still view content and complete exercises without an account, but you will not have full account features (such as seeing your progress in mastering skills and keeping track of your learning activity). You may later enable or access those features by providing Khan Academy with the necessary information to create an account.</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="4.6,6;4.6,6">You can choose to provide information which does not reasonably identify you to others. For example, we recommend you select a username which is not related to your actual name (or could otherwise be used to identify you). You can also decline to provide any optional information in your public profile.</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="6;6">You choose whether (and how) to participate in publicly accessible forums, such as posting to public spaces of the Service. When you post a question (or answer) to the Service (or otherwise participate in a public forum), your profile (as well as the content of your posted comment) is visible to others on the Service. Our Service offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others. Child Users are not able to post in community forums (as described in Children’s Privacy Notice).</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="4.9,6;4.9,6">You choose which third party applications you want to use and can stop using any such third party applications at any time. This functionality is optional, and entirely up to you. For instance, you can revoke Khan Academy’s access to your account on any single sign-on service at any time by updating the appropriate settings in the account preferences of the Authentication Service (or simply by not logging in through that Authentication Service).</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="4.3,4.9,6;4.3,4.9,6">Khan Academy may, from time to time, send you emails regarding our products and Service, or products and services we think you may enjoy. You can choose not to receive these emails by clicking the unsubscribe link in any e-mail or updating your Settings page. Please note that you are not permitted to unsubscribe or opt-out of certain types of messages regarding your account, such as account verification, changes or updates to features of the Service, technical or security notices and certain programmatic communications (such as class assignments).</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="6;6">You can choose to add a coach or teacher to your account so that your coach or teacher can view your account profile and your learning activity on the Service, such as which videos you have watched, the questions and responses you post, and other use information. When your account is connected to a coach, teacher or School on the Service, your coach, teacher or School will be able to see your profile information and your learning activity on the Service. If you link your personal account to a School Account, a connected teacher or School will see your personal learning activity as well as learning activity from School use. A connected coach or teacher may also be able to see your name (not only your username) as well as your email address, if you include that information in your account profile. Please note that some account profile information and teacher connections for certain School Accounts are controlled by the School.</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="4.3,4.9,6;4.3,4.9,6">Many web browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If you prefer, you can usually choose to set your browser to remove or reject browser cookies or to prompt you before accepting such a cookie. You also can directly opt out of certain third party cookies. Please note that choosing to remove or reject certain cookies might limit your use of the Service. For more information about our use of cookies and other similar technologies, please review our Cookie Notice.</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="6;6">We offer clearly marked sharing features, which allow you to share information about courses or topics you are learning about through the Service. Using the sharing features is entirely at your option.</paragraph>
</segment>
	<segment>
		<title tagname="h2" depth="1" font-size="2.12" font-weight="1.0" category="4.3;4.3">
			Your account settings
			</title>
		<paragraph category="4.2,4.3,4.4;4.2,4.3,4.4">We want you to have access to your information, so that you can help keep it as accurate as possible. If you register and provide Khan Academy with information, you may update, correct, or delete your account and information at any time by reviewing your profile information and preferences on your account settings page.</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="4.3,4.4;4.3,4.4">Parents (not Children) can modify or delete Child User accounts, as described in our Children’s Privacy Notice. Parents or school users who request to modify or delete School Accounts may be directed to the School.</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="4.2,4.3,4.4;4.2,4.3,4.4">Further information about how you can access, update, correct, or delete your account in the account settings is provided under “Learn More”.</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="4.2,4.3,4.4;4.2,4.3,4.4">You may access, update, and correct your personal information at any time by logging into your account and updating the relevant information on your account settings page.</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="4.4;4.4">To request deletion of your information at any time, please log into your account and select “delete your account“ through Settings. You can learn more in our Help Center.</paragraph>
		<item>Please note that your information will be retained in backup for up to one week. If you log back into your account within 24 hours, your account willnotbe deleted and you will need to go through the deletion process again.</item>
		<item>We may not be able to delete information in all instances. For example, we may retain certain information as necessary to prevent fraud or future abuse, for recordkeeping or other legitimate business purposes, or if required by law. Retained personal information will remain subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy.</item>
		<item>Unless we receive a deletion request, we will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as is reasonably useful for operational purposes. We may also retain information which has been de-identified or aggregated such that it can no longer reasonably identify a particular individual.</item>
		<item>Parents can modify or delete Child User accounts that are connected to the parent account, except for certain School Accounts.</item>
		<paragraph category="4;4">The default settings for accounts used by or at the direction of a School may differ depending on the manner in which Khan Academy is used by a School and the terms of the agreement between the School and Khan Academy. In some cases, administrative controls including the ability to modify or delete the account, are held by the School. If you have a School Account, please contact your School administrator for information regarding your account. For more information, please review Schools and Student Use.</paragraph>
</segment>
	<segment>
		<title tagname="h2" depth="1" font-size="2.12" font-weight="1.0" category="12;12">
			Security of your personal information
			</title>
		<paragraph category="12;12">Khan Academy is committed to securing your personal information.</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="12;12">Some of the ways in which we protect your personal information include:</paragraph>
		<item>We encrypt your personal information when it is stored at rest</item>
		<item>We protect your personal information with encryption during transmission over the public Internet</item>
		<item>We use reasonable organizational and technical safeguards designed to help protect the privacy and security of your personal information</item>
		<paragraph category="12;12">Some of the ways in which we encourage you to protect your personal information include:</paragraph>
		<item>We encourage you to create a username that does not reveal your identity</item>
		<item>We encourage you to create (and keep) a strong password</item>
		<item>We encourage you to be thoughtful about what you post and continue to learn about online safety</item>
		<paragraph category="12;12">We use reasonable safeguards to protect our Service and your personal information, but no security measures are perfect.</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="4.2,4.3,12;4.2,4.3,12">To protect your privacy and security, we take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting account access or making corrections to your information. For example, we may ask you to provide certain information to confirm your identity, and we may require that you create and use a password to access certain parts of our Service. We strongly encourage you to create and maintain a strong password to help ensure the security of your account.</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="12;12">Khan Academy uses reasonable physical, administrative, and technical safeguards designed to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information we maintain in connection with our Service. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any or all of the information you transmit to Khan Academy. For instance, no Internet service or email message is ever fully secure or error free. In particular, emails sent to or from the Service may not be secure. Please take special care in deciding what information you send to us via email or for support help. Once we receive your transmission of information, Khan Academy makes commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the security of our systems. When you enter sensitive information, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL) or similar technologies. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by a breach of any of our physical, technical, or administrative safeguards. In the event that any information under our control is compromised as a result of a breach of security, we will take reasonable steps to investigate the situation and will notify you of the security incident in accordance with applicable laws and regulations.</paragraph>
</segment>
	<segment>
		<title tagname="h2" depth="1" font-size="2.12" font-weight="1.0" category="19;19">
			Links to Third Parties
			</title>
		<paragraph category="19;19">The Service may link to and may be linked by websites operated by other entities or individuals. If we include links to third parties and you click on that link, you will be leaving Khan Academy and the privacy policy of that third party applies. Similarly, if you see a link to Khan Academy on a third party website, then the privacy policy of that third party applies.</paragraph>
		<item>For example:</item>
		<item>If you click on a link to College Board, then you will go to College Board’s website and College Board’s privacy policy applies.</item>
		<item>If you are on the Khan Academy Instagram page, the privacy policy of Instagram applies to that Khan Academy Instagram page.</item>
		<item>This Khan Academy Privacy Policy does not apply to (and we cannot control the activities of) such other third party websites.</item>
		<item>You should consult the privacy policies of those third party websites.</item>
</segment>
	<segment>
		<title tagname="h2" depth="1" font-size="2.12" font-weight="1.0" category="5;5">
			Changes to this Privacy Policy
			</title>
		<paragraph category="4.1,5;4.1,5">Khan Academy may modify or revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. Khan Academy will notify users of any changes to our Privacy Policy by posting the revised Privacy Policy with an updated date of revision on our Service. If we change this Policy in a material manner, we will do our best to notify you of the changes by posting a notice on our website. We recommend that you review the Privacy Policy each time you visit the Service to stay informed of our privacy practices.</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="5;5">We will not make any material changes to our Privacy Policy that relate to the collection or use of Student Personal Data without first giving notice to the School and providing a choice before Student Personal Data are used in a materially different manner than was disclosed when the information was collected.</paragraph>
</segment>
	<segment>
		<title tagname="h2" depth="1" font-size="2.12" font-weight="1.0" category="1.2;1.2">
			Contact Khan Academy
			</title>
		<paragraph category="1.2;1.2">Please contact Khan Academy with any questions or comments.</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="19;1.2">By email: our Privacy team</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="19;1.2">By mail: Khan Academy, PO Box 1630, Mountain View, CA 94042</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="19;19">You may also wish to visit the Khan Academy Help Center and Common Questions and Resources page, which hosts useful FAQs and information that you may find helpful.</paragraph>
</segment>
	<segment>
		<title tagname="h2" depth="1" font-size="2.12" font-weight="1.0" category="19;19">
			Schools and Student Use
			</title>
		<segment>
			<title tagname="strong" depth="2" font-size="1.12" font-weight="1.75" category="19;19">
				Our commitment:
				</title>
			<paragraph category="18.2;18.2">We are proud supporters of the Student Privacy Pledge. Our collection and use of Student Personal Data is governed by our contracts with Schools, by our Privacy Policy, and by applicable privacy laws. For example, we work with Schools to protect Student Personal Data consistent with FERPA and, for School Users under 13, the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (“COPPA”). If you have any questions about reviewing, modifying, or deleting the personal information of a School User, please contact your School directly.</paragraph>
</segment>
		<segment>
			<title tagname="strong" depth="2" font-size="1.12" font-weight="1.75" category="19;19">
				Creation of School Accounts
				</title>
			<paragraph category="11,15;11,15">Please note that in order for School User accounts to be associated with a School and recognized as School Accounts (as defined in our Terms of Service), the accounts must be created by or at the direction of a School, using a school email address and associated with a School’s class on the Service. For example, a School Account is created when:</paragraph>
		<item>a teacher creates the user name, login and password to establish School User accounts and creates a class on the Service</item>
		<item>a teacher rosters a class using Google Classroom, Clever, or similar single sign-on service for School use</item>
		<item>an account is created by a School User at the direction of a School, using a School email address and associated with a School’s class on the Service</item>
		<item>accounts are created pursuant to a separate contract between Khan Academy and the school district (or educational agency) specifying that the accounts are School Accounts</item>
		<paragraph category="10.1,11;10.1,11">In cases where we do not have a separate contract with a School district or educational agency, we may require notification that the accounts are used for school purposes in order to recognize them as School Accounts. If you are a School, please contact our School Partnerships Team to learn more about how to ensure that student accounts are set up and managed as School Accounts.</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="12,16.1,16.3;12,16.1,16.3">Please review “Learn More” to see more information about:</paragraph>
		<item>Some of the specific ways that we use and protect Student Personal Data</item>
		<item>How we share and disclose Student Personal Data</item>
		<item>No Targeted Advertising</item>
		<item>How we retain and delete Student Personal Data</item>
		<item>Questions about Student Personal Data</item>
		<item>We collect, maintain, use and share Student Personal Data only for authorized educational purposes and as described in our Privacy Policy, including as directed by the School, the School User and/or the student’s parent or legal guardian (a “Parent”).</item>
		<item>We do not disclose Student Personal Data for targeted advertising purposes. We take steps to disable third party ad networks when a School User logs into a School User account on the Service.</item>
		<item>We do not build a personal profile of a School User other than in furtherance of an educational purpose or as authorized by a Parent.</item>
		<item>We have implemented and maintain a data security program designed to protect the types of Student Personal Data collected and used by the Service.</item>
		<item>We will clearly and transparently disclose our data policies and practices to our users.</item>
		<item>We will never sell Student Personal Data unless the sale is part of a corporate transaction, such as a merger, acquisition, bankruptcy, or other sale of assets, in which case we will require the new owner to continue to honor the terms provided in this Privacy Policy or we will provide the School with notice and an opportunity to opt-out of the transfer of Student Personal Data by deleting the Student Personal Data before the transfer occurs.</item>
		<item>We will not make any material changes to our Privacy Policy or contractual agreements that relate to the collection or use of Student Personal Data without first giving notice to the School and providing a choice before the Student Personal Data are used in a materially different manner than was disclosed when the information was collected.</item>
		<paragraph category="17.1,17.2;17.1,17.2">We disclose Student Personal Data in the manner described in our Privacy Policy under the Section entitled Sharing and disclosure of information. In addition, depending on the features and account controls applicable to the School Accounts, we may share information with other users on the Service, such as teachers, coaches, or School administrators. If a School User posts content in a community forum, their username and profile information will be visible along with the comment.</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="10.1,11,17;10.1,11,17">Depending on the manner in which Khan Academy is used by a School and the terms of the agreement between the School and Khan Academy, Khan Academy may provide the School with access to certain Student Personal Data, School Account usage information and teacher user account usage information for school purposes, such as monitoring student learning activity and evaluating the effectiveness of the School’s use of the Service. Khan Academy may also provide Schools with access to Student Personal Data, Student usage information, and teacher usage information in response to a School’s request.</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="17;17">Khan Academy does not use, disclose, or compile Student Personal Data of School Users on the Service for the purpose of marketing or advertising commercial products or services, including targeted advertising.</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="16.1,16.3;16.1,16.3">We will not knowingly retain Student Personal Data beyond the time period required to support an educational purpose, unless authorized to do so by a School, student or Parent. Many of our users continue to use their accounts for a personal, non-School purpose and choose to associate their accounts with a personal account or the account of their Parent. In such cases, the user (or the user’s Parent) is responsible for account deletion requests.</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="4.9;4.9">Users with personal accounts (or their Parents) can delete their accounts and personal information associated with the account at any time through account Settings. See “How can I cancel or delete my account” in the Khan Academy Help Center for instructions.</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="4.9,10.1;4.9,10.1">Depending on the manner in which Khan Academy is used by a School and the terms of an agreement between the School and Khan Academy, users, including School Users (or their Parents) may be able to delete their accounts and personal information associated with the account through account Settings. See “How can I cancel or delete my account” in the Khan Academy Help Center for instructions. In some cases our School partners have implemented Khan Academy through an agreement between Khan Academy and the school district or educational agency that includes additional rostering and administrative services; in these cases, School Users (or their Parents) may not be able to delete accounts through account Settings, and deletion requests may need to be referred to the School.</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="4.4,16;4.4,16">The School is responsible for managing Student Personal Data in accounts that the School no longer needs for an educational purpose by submitting a deletion request. Schools should contact our School Partnerships Team to request deletion of Student Personal Data associated with School Accounts. We may request further information from you to verify the authenticity of a deletion request. If a School User has associated their School Account with a personal account, the School User’s learning activity may be retained in the personal account.</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="19;19">If you have questions about specific practices relating to Student Personal Data provided to Khan Academy by a School, please direct your questions to your School.</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="19;19">This section does not apply to information that a student or other individual may provide to Khan Academy independent of the student’s use of the Service at the direction of the School. For example, if a user links their existing personal account to their School Account, or elects to retain their Khan Academy learning activity in a personal account, the information associated with the personal account is not considered Student Personal Data.</paragraph>
</segment>
		<paragraph category="10;10">This School and Student Use notice supplements our Privacy Policy in connection with school use. Khan Academy is a nonprofit organization dedicated to providing free educational content. We strive to implement best practices to protect the privacy of all of our student and non-student users, alike. We have implemented additional controls and procedures for schools, school districts and teachers (collectively referred to as “Schools”) when they use the Service for educational purposes. When the Service is used as part of the School’s educational program, the personal information related to the School’s student users (“School Users”) may include information defined as “education records” by the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (“FERPA”) or other information protected by similar state student data privacy laws. We refer to this information as “Student Personal Data”.</paragraph>
</segment>
	<segment>
		<title tagname="h2" depth="1" font-size="2.12" font-weight="1.0" category="15;15">
			Children’s Privacy Notice
			</title>
		<segment>
			<title tagname="strong" depth="2" font-size="1.12" font-weight="1.75" category="15;15">
				Khan Academy is committed to Children’s privacy.
				</title>
			<paragraph category="15;15">Protecting the privacy of Children is especially important to Khan Academy. For that reason, we created certain features designed to help protect personal information relating to Children (“Child Users”). When a Child creates an account, we seek the consent of a parent or legal guardian (“Parent”) for that account. When Khan Academy is used by a School in an educational setting, we rely on the School to provide the requisite consent, on behalf of the Parent, for Khan Academy to collect information from a School User under the age of 13.</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="15;15">Please review “Learn More” for more information about:</paragraph>
		<item>How Children can use and register for our Service</item>
		<item>Restrictions placed on Accounts for Child Users</item>
		<item>Information collected and how the information is used</item>
		<item>Information disclosed</item>
		<item>No Third Party Tracking and No Targeted Advertising</item>
		<item>Choice: Access, Modify and Delete Child Accounts</item>
		<paragraph category="11;11">Users may view our content and do exercises without creating an account. Functionality is limited if users do not create an account.</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="10.5;10.5">Khan Academy does not knowingly permit Child Users to create an account without the consent of a Parent or School. If Khan Academy learns that personal information of a Child User has been collected on our Service without Parent or School consent, Khan Academy will take appropriate steps to delete this information. If you are a Parent and discover that your child under the age of 13 has a registered account with our Service without consent, please Contact Khan Academy and request that we delete that child’s personal information from our systems.</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="15;15">Child Users can sign up for a Khan Academy account in one of the following ways:</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="10.5,11;10.5,11">When a Child User registers for our Service, we request a username, birthdate, password, and a Parent’s email address so that we can email the Child User’s Parent in order to seek consent for the Child to use the Service. Khan Academy does not ask the Child User for any more information than is necessary to provide the Service to the Child User or to seek Parent consent. The Child User is permitted to use the Service for 7 days through a Restricted Account while we notify the Parent and request consent. If we do not receive consent from the Parent within 7 days, the Child User’s Restricted Account is closed, and the Child’s personal information is deleted from our systems. Khan Academy may rely on a School to provide consent on behalf of a Parent, as described below.</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="10.5,11;10.5,11">When the Khan Academy Service is used by a School in an educational setting, we permit the School to create Child User accounts and to provide the requisite consent, on behalf of the Child User’s Parent, for Khan Academy to collect personal information of a Child User for this purpose. Schools may create a Child User account by adding students to the Service through Google Classroom, Clever, or similar Single Sign On service, providing a link or class code to join a class, or a School may create logins and passwords for each individual student. When Schools create accounts in this manner, we rely on the consent provided to us by the School and do not require additional consent from the Parent.</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="10.5,11;10.5,11">Parents may provide consent for a Child User to use the Service through a Restricted Account by responding affirmatively to an email sent by Khan Academy to the Parent’s email address provided by the Child User during registration. If we do not receive consent from the Parent (or confirmation that the account is a School Account) within 7 days, the Child User’s account will be closed and the Child’s personal information will be deleted from our systems. Restricted Accounts may access and use certain features of the Service in a limited manner.</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="10.5,11;10.5,11">To enable additional functionality for the Child User account and to enable full access and control over the Child User’s account activity, the Parent must create a “Parent Account” on the Service and connect to the Child User’s account by clicking on the account creation link in the Parental consent notice. Parent Accounts control the settings and functionality of the Child User’s account. The Parent can maintain the Child’s Restricted Account, and can enable additional account functionality and features, if desired. Parents can revoke a Child User’s permissions to use the Service at any time by deleting the account. In some cases, administrative controls including the ability to modify or delete the account, are held by the School.</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="15;15">Khan Academy attempts to restrict a Child User’s access to certain features that could result in disclosure of the Child’s personal information. A Restricted Account limits sharing and displaying private information about the Child User in various ways.</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="15;15">For example, a Child User with a Restricted Account cannot:</paragraph>
		<item>Display personal information other than a username. Restricted Accounts contain the Child’s username and do not include other personal information or profile information. Because the username may be displayed on the Service, we strongly recommend selecting a username that does not relate to or identify the real name of the Child. The Child’s username can be selected or revised by the Parent by creating a Parent Account.</item>
		<item>Add or edit personal information associated with a Restricted Account.</item>
		<item>Post to public community forums, or post questions or answers on lessons.</item>
		<item>Receive emails from Khan Academy (all emails are sent to the Parent email on file).</item>
		<item>Communicate with or share personal information with Coaches other than a username and Service usage activity (i.e., lessons completed, badges earned, etc.). Similarly, Coaches cannot communicate with a Child User with a Restricted Account except to assign content for the Child User.</item>
		<paragraph category="8,9,11;8,9,11">We collect a username, birthdate, and Parent’s email address when a Child User registers for the Service, as well as any other personal information a Parent adds to a Child User’s account, as described above. We collect information about the Child User’s use of the Service (lessons completed, badges earned). We also collect usage and device information, as described in Collection of information.</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="11;11">We use this information to provide the Service and for the purposes described in Use of information. We use the Parent’s email address to communicate messages about the account.</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="17;17">As described above, Restricted Accounts have limited information sharing capabilities. A username and progress information, along with any personal information the Parent added to the Child’s profile, is shared with a Coach or teacher added to the Child User’s account, though a Parent Account may restrict the Child User from adding Coaches to the account. Parents may also enable additional information sharing features through a Parent Account, for example, by adding profile information and permitting the profile to be shared with Coaches and other users, or enabling the Child User to post content (e.g., questions and answers) to the Service. Parents that enable content-posting features should be aware that a Child User could post personally identifiable information in free-form content on the Service, and should monitor the Child User’s posts and delete personal information if needed. We may also disclose personal information of Child Users for business purposes, as described in Sharing and disclosure of information.</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="19;19">Khan Academy does not display any targeted advertising on the Service. We do not disclose personal information of Child Users for direct marketing purposes or for targeted advertising purposes. In addition, we take steps to disable third party ad networks on webpages with child-directed content or when a Child User logs into a Restricted Account on the Service.</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="4.2,4.3,4.4;4.2,4.3,4.4">As a Parent, you have the ability to access and control information about your Child User in the “Your Children” section of your Parent Account. To refuse future collection or use of your child’s personal information, you can delete your Child User’s Account by following the instructions in our FAQ. Please note, you must delete your Child User’s accountbeforeyou delete the Parent Account.</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="4.2,4.9;4.2,4.9">If you do not have a Parent Account associated with your Child User’s Restricted Account, you may contact us at our Support page to access or delete the Child User’s account. Please note you will need the Child User’s username, and we may take steps to authenticate your identity before we can provide access to the Restricted Account.</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="4.3.4.4;4.3,4.4">In some cases, administrative controls including the ability to modify or delete the account, are held by the School and you will need to direct your request to the School. For more information, please review Schools and Student Use.</paragraph>
</segment>
		<paragraph category="15;15">This privacy notice supplements our Privacy Policy and provides additional information about how we collect, use and share personal information from children under the age of 13 (a “Child” or “Children”).</paragraph>
</segment>
	<segment>
		<title tagname="h2" depth="1" font-size="2.12" font-weight="1.0" category="19;19">
			Donor information
			</title>
		<paragraph category="8,9;8,9">This Donor information notice supplements our Privacy Policy in connection with donors. If you donate to Khan Academy and do not donate anonymously, we obtain information such as your name, email address, and mailing address. If you donate using our online form, our payment processor will also collect your credit or debit card number or other payment information. Please note that information collected by these payment processors is subject to their own privacy policy.</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="11;11">We may use donor information to communicate with you about your contribution and to send fundraising updates and information regarding the advancement of our mission.</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="10.5,17;10.5,17">We do not share personally identifiable donor information except with your consent or as required by law.</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="4.3,4.9;4.3,4.9">If you have registered for an account with us, then you may update your preferences in your account settings to opt out of donor emails. If you do not have an account with us, then you may opt out by clicking the unsubscribe link on the donor email message or responding back to the email asking to be removed. Please note that if you have previously unsubscribed but subsequently donate (or attend a donor event), then we may send you follow up communications regarding your support of our mission.</paragraph>
		<item>We will not sell, share or trade our donors' names or personal information with any other entity, nor send mailings to our donors on behalf of other organizations.</item>
		<item>We will not send you mailings on behalf of other organizations.</item>
		<item>We will collect payment information, billing address and other information necessary to process a donation or event registration.</item>
		<item>We will use your information to comply with the law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to conform to the requirements of law or comply with legal process served on us.</item>
		<item>We may use the personal information to protect against potential fraud. We may verify with third parties the information collected in the course of processing a gift, event registration or other donation.</item>
		<item>If you use a credit or debit card on the website, we may use card authorization and fraud screening services to verify that your card information and address matches the information that you supplied to us and that the card being used has not been reported lost or stolen.</item>
</segment>
	<segment>
		<title tagname="h2" depth="1" font-size="2.12" font-weight="1.0" category="19;19">
			Applicant information
			</title>
		<paragraph category="4.2,4.3,4.4,4.5,4.6,4.7;4.2,4.3,4.4,4.5,4.6,4.7">This Applicant information notice supplements our Privacy Policy in connection with applicants. If you apply for a job with Khan Academy via an online application or recruiting site, we will obtain the information you choose to provide in your application for that purpose. For example, we collect professional or employment-related information that typically includes details regarding your employment history, experience, and qualifications; as well as education information, including degrees obtained and academic records.</paragraph>
		<item>Right of access and portability. The right to obtain access to your personal information, along with certain related information, and to receive that information in a commonly used format and to have it transferred to another data controller</item>
		<item>Right to rectification. The right to obtain rectification of your personal information without undue delay where that personal information is inaccurate or incomplete</item>
		<item>Right to erasure. The right to obtain the erasure of your personal information without undue delay in certain circumstances, such as where the personal information is no longer necessary in relation to the purposes for which it was collected or processed</item>
		<item>Right to restriction. The right to obtain the restriction of the processing undertaken by us on your personal information in certain circumstances, such as where the accuracy of the personal information is contested by you, for a period enabling us to verify the accuracy of that personal information</item>
		<item>Right to object.The right to object, on grounds relating to your particular situation, to the processing of your personal information, and to object to processing of your personal information for direct marketing purposes, to the extent it is related to such direct marketing</item>
		<item>The processing is necessary to perform our contractual obligations in our Terms of Service or other contracts with you</item>
		<item>The processing is necessary for the purposes of our legitimate interests, such as in improving, personalizing, and developing the Service, marketing the Service, such as new features or products that may be of interest, and promoting safety and security as described above</item>
		<item>You give us consent to do so for a specific purpose</item>
		<item>The processing is necessary to comply with a legal obligation, a court order or to exercise or defend legal claims</item>
</segment>
	<segment>
		<title tagname="h2" depth="1" font-size="2.12" font-weight="1.0" category="8;19">
			Regional information
			</title>
		<paragraph category="8,9;8,9">This Regional information notice supplements our Privacy Policy. In certain regions, you may have certain additional rights. This may include the right to request access or to update or review your information, request that it be deleted or anonymized, or object to or restrict Khan Academy using it for certain purposes.</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="4;4">If you wish to exercise a right, please Contact Khan Academy. Our ability to respond to specific requests may be limited by applicable law and the functionality of our Service.</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="14.1;14.1">International Data Transfer : Our Service is operated and managed on servers located within the United States. If you choose to use our Service from Europe or other regions of the world with laws governing data collection and use that differ from United States law, then you acknowledge that Khan Academy will transfer, store, and process your personal information to the United States for the purpose of performing the Service according to our contract (e.g., our Terms of Service) and for any other purpose for which you provide explicit, informed consent.</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="18.2;18.2">California Minors' Rights</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="18.2;18.2">If you are a registered user under the age of 18 residing in California, you are entitled to request removal of content or information you have posted publicly on our Service. To request removal, please Contact Khan Academy for assistance. Please note that your request does not ensure complete or comprehensive removal, as the content or information may be retained subject to applicable law.</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="7;7">You may also have the right to make a complaint to the relevant Supervisory Authority. If you need further assistance regarding your rights, please contact us and we will consider your request in accordance with applicable law. In some cases our ability to uphold these rights for you may depend upon our obligations to process personal information for security, safety, fraud prevention reasons, compliance with regulatory or legal requirements, or because processing is necessary to deliver the services you have requested. Where this is the case, we will inform you of specific details in response to your request.</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="10;10">For personal data subject to the GDPR, we rely on several legal bases to process the data. These legal bases include where:</paragraph>
</segment>
</policy>