<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<policy>
	<url>https://www.  .com</url>
	<update_time>20/ /</update_time>
	<download_time>2021/02/18</download_time>
	<paragraph category="">Privacy &amp; Cookie Statement </paragraph>
	<segment>
		<title tagname="h2" depth="1" font-size="2.0" font-weight="1.5">Privacy Statement</title>
		<paragraph>Jun 25, 2021 First things first – your privacy is important to us. That might be the kind of thing all these notices say, but we mean it. You place your trust in us by using Booking.com services, and we value that trust. That means we’re committed to protecting and safeguarding any personal data you give us. We act in our customers' interest and are transparent about the processing of your personal data. This document describes how we use and process your personal data, provided in a readable and transparent manner. It also tells you what rights you can exercise in relation to your personal data (such as the right to object) and how to contact us. Please also read our Cookie Statement , which tells you how Booking.com uses cookies and other similar technologies. If you’ve used us before, you know that Booking.com offers online travel-related services through our own websites and mobile apps, as well as other online platforms such as partners’ websites and social media. We’d like to point out that all the info you’re about to read generally applies to not one, not two, but all of these platforms. In fact, this single privacy statement applies to any kind of customer info we collect through all of the above platforms or by any other means connected to these platforms, such as when you contact our customer service team by email. If you're one of our business partners, check out our Privacy Statement for Business Partners to understand how personal data is further processed as part of the business relationship. We might amend the Privacy Statement from time to time, so we recommend revisiting this page occasionally to make sure you know where you stand. If we make changes to the Privacy Statement which will have an impact on you (e.g. if we intend to process your personal data for other purposes than previously communicated), we'll notify you of these changes before the new activities begin. And now, the sad but necessary part: If you disagree with this Privacy Statement, you should discontinue using our services. If you agree with our Privacy Statement, then you’re all set to book your next trip through us. </paragraph>
		<segment>
			<title tagname="h3" depth="1" font-size="1.5" font-weight="1.5">Terms we use in this Privacy Statement</title>
			<paragraph>“Trip” refers to the various different travel products and services that can be ordered, acquired, purchased, bought, paid, rented, provided, reserved, combined, or consummated by you from the Trip Provider. “Trip Provide” refers to the provider of accommodation (e.g. hotel, motel, apartment, bed &amp; breakfast, landlord), attractions (e.g. (theme) parks, museums, sightseeing tours), transportation provider (e.g. car rentals, cruises, trains, flights, bus tours, transfers), tour operators, travel insurances, and any other travel or related product or service as from time to time available for Trip Reservation on the platform. “Trip Service” refers to the online purchase, order, (facilitated) payment, or reservation service as offered or enabled by Booking.com in regards to various products and services as from time to time made available by Trip Providers on the platform. “Trip Reservation” refers to the order, purchase, payment, booking, or reservation of a Trip. </paragraph>
		</segment>
		<segment>
			<title tagname="h3" depth="1" font-size="1.5" font-weight="1.5" category="8,9;8,9">What kind of personal data does Booking.com collect?</title>
			<paragraph category="8,9.1;8,9.1">We can’t help you book the perfect Trip without information, so when you use our services there are certain things we ask for. This is typically routine info – your name, preferred contact details, the names of the people traveling with you, and your payment info. You might also decide to submit additional info related to your upcoming Trip (e.g. your anticipated arrival time). </paragraph>
			<paragraph category="8,9.2,9.3;8,9.2,9.3">In addition to this, we also collect info from the computer, phone, tablet, or other device you use to access our services. This includes the <item>IP address</item>, the browser used, and your language settings. There are also situations when we receive info about you from others or automatically collect other info. </paragraph>
			<paragraph category="8,9;8,9">This is just a general overview. If you’d like to learn more about the info we collect, we go into more detail below. </paragraph>
		</segment>
		<segment>
			<title tagname="h3" depth="1" font-size="1.5" font-weight="1.5" category="11;11">Why does Booking.com collect and use your personal data?</title>
			<paragraph category="11;11">The main reason we ask for personal details is to help you organize your online Trip Reservations and ensure you get the best possible service. </paragraph>
			<paragraph category="11;11">We also use your personal data to contact you about the latest deals, special offers, and other products or services we think you might be interested in. There are other uses, too. If you’d like to find out what they are, read on for a more detailed explanation. </paragraph>
		</segment>
		<segment>
			<title tagname="h3" depth="1" font-size="1.5" font-weight="1.5" category="17;17">How does Booking.com share your data with third parties?</title>
			<paragraph category="17.1,17.2;17.1,17.2">There are different parties integrated into Booking.com’s services, in various ways and for various reasons. The primary reason we share your data is to provide the Trip Provider with the relevant info to complete your Trip Reservation. </paragraph>
			<paragraph category="17.1,17.2;17.1,17.2">We also involve other parties to provide you Booking.com services. This includes, for example, financial institutions, advertisers, subsidiaries of the Booking.com corporate group, and other affiliates of the Booking Holdings Inc. corporate group. In some cases, if we’re required by law, we might share your data with governmental or other authorities. </paragraph>
			<paragraph category="17;17">We’ll go into more detail about how the info you share with us is used and exchanged with these parties below.  </paragraph>
		</segment>
		<segment>
			<title tagname="h3" depth="1" font-size="1.5" font-weight="1.5" category="17;17">How is your personal data shared within the Booking Holdings Inc. corporate group?</title>
			<paragraph category="17;17">Booking.com is part of the Booking Holdings Inc. corporate group. Read on to learn how your data may be shared within the Booking Holdings corporate group.  </paragraph>
		</segment>
		<segment>
			<title tagname="h3" depth="1" font-size="1.5" font-weight="1.5" category="17;17">How is your personal data shared and further processed for ground transportation services?</title>
			<paragraph category="17.1,17.2;17.1,17.2">Booking.com and Rentalcars.com—also part of the Booking Holdings Inc. group of companies—jointly use your data to offer you ground transport services via the Booking.com websites and apps (such as cars.booking.com or taxi.booking.com). Read more to understand the scope and limited nature of our joint responsibility.</paragraph>
		</segment>
		<segment>
			<title tagname="h3" depth="1" font-size="1.5" font-weight="1.5" category="11;11">How does Booking.com process communications that you and your Trip Provider may send via Booking.com?</title>
			<paragraph category="11;11">Booking.com can help you and Trip Providers exchange info or requests about services and existing Trip Reservations through the Booking.com platform. To find out more about how Booking.com receives and handles these communications, read on here. </paragraph>
		</segment>
		<segment>
			<title tagname="h3" depth="1" font-size="1.5" font-weight="1.5" category="11;11">How does Booking.com make use of mobile devices?</title>
			<paragraph category="11;11">We offer free apps that we also collect and process personal data through. This works in a similar way to our website, but they also allow you to benefit from the location services available on your mobile device(s). </paragraph>
		</segment>
		<segment>
			<title tagname="h3" depth="1" font-size="1.5" font-weight="1.5" category="11;11">How does Booking.com make use of social media?</title>
			<paragraph category="11;11">The use of social media may be integrated into Booking.com services in various ways. These will involve us collecting some of your personal data, or the social media provider receiving some of your info. If you’d like to learn more about how this info is used and exchanged, read on. </paragraph>
		</segment>
		<segment>
			<title tagname="h3" depth="1" font-size="1.5" font-weight="1.5" category="12;12">What security and retention procedures does Booking.com put in place to safeguard your personal data?</title>
			<paragraph category="12;12">We’ve implemented a range of procedures to prevent unauthorized access to and the misuse of personal data that we process. </paragraph>
		</segment>
		<segment>
			<title tagname="h3" depth="1" font-size="1.5" font-weight="1.5" category="15;15">How does Booking.com treat personal data belonging to children?</title>
			<paragraph category="15;15">Unless indicated otherwise, Booking.com is a service you’re only allowed to use if over you’re older than 16. We only process info about children with the consent of their parents or legal guardians or when the info is provided for use by the parents or legal guardians.  </paragraph>
		</segment>
		<segment>
			<title tagname="h3" depth="1" font-size="1.5" font-weight="1.5" category="4;4">How can you control the personal data you’ve given to Booking.com?</title>
			<paragraph category="4.2,4.4;4.2,4.4">You have the right to review the personal data we keep about you at any time. You can request access to or deletion of your personal data by submitting this form . If you want to find out more about your rights to control your personal data, read on. </paragraph>
		</segment>
		<segment>
			<title tagname="h3" depth="1" font-size="1.5" font-weight="1.5" category="19;19">Who is responsible for the processing of personal data on the Booking.com website and apps?</title>
			<paragraph category="1.1;1.1">Booking.com B.V., located in Amsterdam, The Netherlands, controls the processing of personal data for the provision of its services. That includes its websites and mobile apps, except for some exceptions that are clarified in this privacy statement. </paragraph>
			<segment>
				<title tagname="h4" depth="1" font-size="1.25" font-weight="1.25" category="19;19">Country-specific provisions</title>
				<paragraph category="10;10">Depending on the law that applies to you, we might be required to provide some additional info. If you'd like to learn more, continue reading. </paragraph>
			</segment>
		</segment>
		<segment>
			<title tagname="h3" depth="1" font-size="1.5" font-weight="1.5" category="8,9;8,9">What kind of personal data does Booking.com collect?</title>
			<paragraph category="8,9;8,9">Depending on the law that applies to you, we might be required to provide some additional info. If you'd like to learn more, continue reading. </paragraph>
			<segment>
				<title tagname="h4" depth="1" font-size="1.25" font-weight="1.25" category="8,9.1;8,9.1">Personal data you give to us.</title>
				<paragraph category="8,9.1;8,9.1">Booking.com collects and uses the info you provide us. When you make a Trip Reservation, you are (at a minimum) asked for your name and email address. </paragraph>
				<paragraph category="8,9.1;8,9.1">Depending on the Trip Reservation, we might also ask for your home address, phone number, payment info, date of birth, the names of any guests traveling with you, and any preferences (e.g. meal preferences, mobility restrictions) you have for your Trip. </paragraph>
				<paragraph category="8,9.1;8,9.1">If you need to get in touch with our customer service team, contact your Trip Provider through us, or reach out to us in a different way (e.g. social media), we’ll collect info from you there, too. This applies whether you’re contacting us with feedback or asking for help using our services. </paragraph>
				<paragraph category="8,9.1;8,9.1">You might also be invited to write reviews to help inform others about the experiences you had on your Trip. When you write a review on the Booking.com platform, we’ll collect any info you’ve included, along with your display name and avatar (if you choose one). </paragraph>
				<paragraph category="8,9.2;8,9.2">There are other instances where you’ll provide us with info, as well. For example, if you’re browsing with your mobile device, you can decide to allow Booking.com to see your current location or grant us access to your contacts. This helps us give you the best possible service and experience by, for example, showing you our city guides, suggesting restaurants and attractions close to your location, or making other recommendations. </paragraph>
				<paragraph category="8,9.1;8,9.1">If you create a user account, we’ll also store your personal settings, uploaded photos, and reviews of previous bookings. This saved data can be used to help you plan and manage future Trip Reservations or benefit from other features only available to account holders, such as incentives or other benefits. </paragraph>
				<paragraph category="8,9.1;8,9.1">We may offer you referral programs or sweepstakes. Participating in these will involve providing us with relevant personal data. </paragraph>
			</segment>
			<segment>
				<title tagname="h4" depth="1" font-size="1.25" font-weight="1.25" category="8,9.1;8,9.1">Personal data you give us about others.</title>
				<paragraph category="8,9.1;8,9.1">Of course, you might not just be making a Trip Reservation for yourself. You might be taking a Trip with other people or making a reservation on someone else’s behalf. In both scenarios, you’ll provide their details as part of the Trip Reservation. </paragraph>
				<paragraph category="19;8,9">If you have a Booking.com for Business account, you can also keep an address book to make it easier to plan and manage business travel arrangements for others. </paragraph>
				<paragraph category="17;17">In some cases, you might use Booking.com to share info with others. This can take the form of sharing a wish list or participating in a referral program, as described when you use the relevant feature. </paragraph>
				<paragraph category="10.5;10.5">At this point, we have to make it clear that it’s your responsibility to ensure that the person or people you provide personal data about are aware that you’ve done so and that they’ve understood and accepted how Booking.com uses their info (as described in this Privacy Statement). </paragraph>
			</segment>
			<segment>
				<title tagname="h4" depth="1" font-size="1.25" font-weight="1.25" category="8,9.2;8,9.2">Personal data we collect automatically.</title>
				<paragraph category="8,9.2;8,9.2">Whether or not you end up making a Trip Reservation, when you visit our websites or apps, we automatically collect certain info. This includes your <item>IP address</item>, the date and time you accessed our services, the hardware, software, or internet browser you used, and info about your computer’s operating system like application versions and your language settings. We also collect information about clicks and which pages were shown to you. </paragraph>
				<paragraph category="8,9.2;8,9.2">If you’re using a mobile device, we collect data that identifies the device, as well as data about your device-specific settings and characteristics, app crashes, and other system activity. When you make a Trip Reservation using this kind of device, our system registers how you made your reservation (on which website), and/or which site you came from when you entered the Booking.com website or app. </paragraph>
			</segment>
			<segment>
				<title tagname="h4" depth="1" font-size="1.25" font-weight="1.25" category="8,9.3;8,9.3">Personal data we receive from other sources.</title>
				<paragraph category="8,9.3;8,9.3">It’s not just the things you tell us, though – we may also receive info about you from other sources. These include business partners, such as affiliate partners, subsidiaries of the Booking.com corporate group, other affiliates of the Booking Holdings Inc. corporate group, and other independent third parties. </paragraph>
				<paragraph category="8,9.3;8,9.3">Anything we receive from these partners may be combined with info provided by you. For example, Booking.com Trip Reservation services aren’t only made available via Booking.com and the Booking.com apps, but are also integrated into services of affiliate partners you can find online. When you use any of these services, you provide the reservation details to our business partners who then forward your details to us. </paragraph>
				<paragraph category="8,9.3,11;8,9.3,11">We also integrate with third party service providers to facilitate payments between you and Trip Providers. These service providers share payment information, so we can administer and handle your Trip Reservation, making sure everything goes as smoothly as possible for you. </paragraph>
				<paragraph category="8,9.3,7;8,9.3,7">We also collect info when we receive a complaint about you from a Trip Provider (e.g. in the case of misconduct). </paragraph>
				<paragraph category="8,9.3;8,9.3">Another way we might receive data about you is through the communication services integrated into our platforms. These communication services offer you a way to contact the Trip Provider you’ve booked with to discuss your stay. In some cases, we receive metadata about these communication activities (e.g. who you are, where you called from, and the date and length of the call). </paragraph>
				<paragraph category="8,9.3,11;8,9.3,11">We may also receive info about you in order to show you more relevant ads, such as the additional cookie data Booking.com social media partners make available to us. Please read the section </paragraph>
				<paragraph category="4.6,8,9.3;4.6,8,9.3">When you link your Booking.com user account to a social media account, you might exchange data between Booking.com and that social media provider. You can always choose not to share that data. </paragraph>
				<paragraph category="8,9.3;8,9.3">Trip Providers may share info about you with Booking.com, too. This could happen if you have support questions about a pending Trip Reservation, or if disputes or other issues arise about a Trip Reservation. </paragraph>
			</segment>
		</segment>
		<segment>
			<title tagname="h3" depth="1" font-size="1.5" font-weight="1.5" category="11;11">Why does Booking.com collect and use your personal data?</title>
			<paragraph category="11;11">We use the info collected about you for various purposes. Your personal data may be used in the following ways: <item>Trip Reservations: First and foremost, we use your personal data to complete and administer your online Trip Reservation, which is essential for what we do. This includes sending you communications that relate to your Trip Reservation, such as confirmations, modifications, and reminders.</item> <item>Customer service: We provide international customer service from our local offices in more than 20 languages and are here to help 24/7. Sharing relevant details such as reservation info or info about your user account with our global customer service staff allows us to respond when you need us. This includes helping you to contact the right Trip Provider and responding to any questions you might have about your Trip Reservation (or any other questions, for that matter).</item><item> Account facilities: Booking.com users can create an account on our website or apps. We use the info you give us to administer this account, enabling you to do a number of useful things. You can manage your Trip Reservations, take advantage of special offers, make future Trip Reservations easily, and manage your personal settings. Managing personal settings lets you keep and share lists, share photos, view previously searched Trip Services, and check other travel-related info you've provided. You can also see any reviews you’ve written. If you want, you can share certain info as part of your user account by creating a public profile under your own first name or a screen name you choose. If you’re a Booking.com for Business account holder, you can also save contact details under that account, manage business reservations, and link other account holders to the same Booking.com for Business account. </item><item>Online groups: We might give account holders the chance to connect and interact with each other through online groups or forums.</item><item> Marketing activities: We use your information for marketing activities. These activities include: <item>Using your contact info to send you regular news about travel-related products and services. You can unsubscribe from email marketing communications quickly, easily, and anytime. All you need to do is click the “Unsubscribe” link included in each newsletter or other communication.</item> <item>Based on your info, individualized offers might be shown to you on the Booking.com website, on mobile apps, or on third-party websites/apps (including social media sites), and the content of the site displayed to you might be personalized. These could be offers that you can book directly on the Booking.com website, on co-branded sites, or other third-party offers or products we think you might find interesting.</item> <item>When you participate in other promotional activities (e.g. sweepstakes, referral programs, or competitions), relevant info will be used to administer these promotions.</item> </item>Communicating with you: There might be other times when we get in touch, including by email, mail, phone, or text. Which method we choose depends on the contact info you previously shared. We process the communications you send to us. There could be a number of reasons for this, including: <item>Responding to and handling any requests you or your booked Trip Provider have made. Booking.com also offers customers and Trip Providers various ways to exchange info, requests, and comments about Trip Providers and existing Trip Reservations via Booking.com. For more info, read the section titled “How does Booking.com process communications that you and your booked Trip Provider may send through Booking.com? .”</item> <item>If you haven't finalized a Trip Reservation online, we can contact you with a reminder to continue with your reservation. We believe this additional service benefits you because it allows you to carry on with a Trip Reservation without having to search for Trip Providers or enter your reservation details again.</item> <item>When you use our services, we might send you a questionnaire or invite you to provide a review about your experience with Booking.com or the Trip Provider.</item> <item>We also send you other material related to your Trip Reservations, such as how to contact Booking.com if you need assistance while you’re away, and information that we feel might be useful to you in planning or making the most of your Trip. We might also send you material related to upcoming Trip Reservations or a summary of previous Trip Reservations you made through Booking.com.</item> <item>Even if you don’t have an upcoming Trip Reservation, we may still need to send you other administrative messages, which could include security alerts.</item> <item>Market research</item>: We sometimes invite our customers to take part in market research. Review the info that accompanies this kind of invitation to understand what personal data will be collected and how it’s used.</item><item> Improving our services: We also use personal data for analytical purposes and product improvement. This is part of our commitment to improving our services and enhancing the user experience. In this case, we use data for testing and troubleshooting purposes, as well as generating statistics about our business. The main goal here is to get insights into how our services perform, how they’re used, and ultimately to optimize and customize our website and apps, making them easier and more meaningful to use. We strive to use pseudonyms for this analytical work as much as possible. </item><item>Providing the best price applicable to you, depending on where you’re based: When you search our apps or website (e.g. to find an accommodation, rental car, or flight), we process your <item>IP address</item> to confirm whether you’re in the European Economic Area (EEA) or another country. We do this to offer you the best price for the region (EEA) or country (non-EEA) where you’re based.</item><item> Customer reviews and other destination-related info: During and after your Trip, we might invite you to submit a review. We can also make it possible for the people you’re traveling with or whom you booked a reservation for to do this instead. This invite asks for info about the Trip Provider or the destination. If you have a Booking.com account, you can choose to display a screen name next to your review instead of your real name ,or even submit the review anonymously. If you’d like to set a screen name, you can do so in your account settings. Adding an avatar is also possible. By completing a review, you’re agreeing that it can be displayed (as described in detail in our Terms and Conditions ) on, for example, the relevant Trip Provider info page on our websites, on our mobile apps, on our social media accounts and social media apps, or on the online platform of the relevant Trip Provider or business partner’s website. This is to inform other travelers about the quality of the Trip Service you used, the destination you have chosen, or any other experiences you choose to share. </item>Call monitoring: When you make calls to our customer service team, Booking.com uses an automated telephone number detection system to match your telephone number to your existing reservations. This helps save time for both you and our customer service staff. However, our customer service staff may still ask for authentication, which helps to keep your reservation details confidential. During calls with our customer service team, live listening might be carried out or calls might be recorded for quality control and training purposes. This includes the use of the recordings for handling of complaints, legal claims, and fraud detection. Not all calls are recorded. Recordings are kept for a limited amount of time before being automatically deleted. An exception to this rule is when Booking.com has a legitimate need to keep the recordings longer for fraud investigation or legal purposes.<item> Promotion of a safe and trustworthy service: To create a trustworthy environment for you, the people you bring with you on your Trip, Booking.com’s business partners, and our Trip Providers, we might use personal data to detect and prevent fraud and other illegal or unwanted activities. Similarly, we might use personal data for risk assessment and security purposes, including the authentication of users and reservations. When we do this we may have to stop or put certain Trip Reservations on hold until we finish our assessment. </item>Legal purposes: Finally, in certain cases, we may need to use your info to handle and resolve legal disputes, for regulatory investigations and compliance to enforce the Booking.com online reservation service terms of use, or to comply with legal requests from law enforcement. Providing your personal data to Booking.com is voluntary. However, we may only be able to provide you with certain services if we can only collect some personal data. For example, we can’t process your Trip Reservation if we don’t collect your name and contact details. If we use automation to process personal data that produces legal effects or significantly affects you, we’ll always implement the measures required to safeguard your rights and freedoms. This includes the right to obtain human intervention. </paragraph>
			<segment>
				<title tagname="h4" depth="1" font-size="1.25" font-weight="1.25" category="10;10">To process your personal data as described above, we rely on the following legal bases:</title>
				<paragraph category="10.1;10.1">As applicable, for purpose A and B, Booking.com relies on the legal basis that the processing of personal data is necessary for the performance of a contract, specifically to finalize and administer your Trip Reservation. </paragraph>
				<paragraph category="10.3;10.3">If the required personal data isn’t provided, Booking.com can’t finalize the Trip Reservation, nor can we provide customer service. In view of purposes C to L, Booking.com relies on its legitimate commercial business interest to provide its services, prevent fraud, and improve our services (as set out more specifically under C to L). </paragraph>
				<paragraph category="10.3,10.6;10.3,10.6">When using personal data to serve Booking.com’s or a third party's legitimate interest, Booking.com will always balance your rights and interests in the protection of your personal data against Booking.com’s rights and interests or those of the third party. For purpose M, Booking.com also relies, where applicable, on compliance with legal obligations (such as legal law enforcement requests). </paragraph>
				<paragraph category="10.5;10.5">Finally, when required under law, Booking.com will obtain your consent prior to processing your personal data, including for email marketing purposes or as otherwise required by law. </paragraph>
				<paragraph category="4.6,1.2;4.6,1.2">If you wish to object to the processing set out under C to L and no opt-out mechanism is available to you directly (for example, in your account settings), contact us at dataprotectionoffice@booking.com . </paragraph>
			</segment>
		</segment>
		<segment>
			<title tagname="h3" depth="1" font-size="1.5" font-weight="1.5" category="17.1,17.2;17.1,17.2">How does Booking.com share your data with third parties?</title>
			<paragraph category="17.1;17.1">In certain circumstances, we’ll share your personal data with third parties. These third parties include:<item> The Trip Provider You Booked: In order to complete your Trip Reservation, we transfer relevant reservation details to the Trip Provider you've booked. This is one of the most essential things we do for you. Depending on the Trip Reservation and Trip Provider, the details we share can include your name, contact and payment details, the names of the people accompanying you, and any other info or preferences you specified when you made your Trip Reservation. In certain cases, we also provide some additional historical info about you to the Trip Provider. This includes whether you’ve already booked with them in the past, the number of completed bookings you’ve made with Booking.com, a confirmation that no misconduct has been reported about you, the percentage of bookings you’ve canceled in the past, or whether you’ve given reviews about past bookings. If you have a question about your Trip, we may contact the Trip Provider to handle your request. Unless payment is made during the booking process through the Booking.com website, we’ll forward your credit card details to the booked Trip Provider for handling (assuming you provide us those details). In cases of Trip Reservation-related disputes, we may provide the Trip Provider with your contact details, including your email address and info about the Trip Reservation process needed to handle the dispute. This may include a copy of your reservation confirmation as proof that a Trip Reservation was actually made. Sometimes, at the direction of the Trip Provider, we’ll need to share your personal data with parties related to the Trip Provider to finalize and administer your reservation. These parties might include other entities of a hotel group or service providers who are handling the data on the Trip Provider’s behalf. </item>Your local Booking.com office: To support the use of Booking.com services, your details may be shared with subsidiaries of the Booking.com corporate group, including for customer service. To find out more about the Booking.com corporate group, visit About Booking.com . Third-party service providers: We use service providers outside of the Booking.com corporate group to support us in providing our services. These include:<list> <item>Customer support</item> <item>Market research</item> <item>Fraud detection and prevention (including anti-fraud screening)</item><item> Payment We use third parties to process payments, handle chargebacks or provide billing collection services. When a chargeback is requested for your Trip Reservation, either by you or the holder of the credit card used to make the reservation, we’ll need to share certain reservation details with the payment service provider and the relevant financial institution so they can handle the chargeback. This could also include a copy of your reservation confirmation or the <item>IP address</item> used to make your reservation. We might share information with relevant financial institutions if we consider it strictly necessary for fraud detection and prevention purposes. </item>Marketing services We share personal data with advertising partners, including your email address, as part of marketing Booking.com services via third parties to ensure that relevant ads are shown to the right audience. We use techniques like hashing to enable the matching of your email address with an existing customer database so that your email address can’t be used for other purposes. For info about other personalized ads and your choices, read our Cookie Statement.<item> Advertising partners We use advertising partners like metasearch providers to allow you to compare our offers with the offers of other Online Travel Agencies (OTAs). When you make a reservation on Booking.com after using an advertising partner, we’ll send the details of the reservation that you made on Booking.com to that partner. </item></list>All service providers are required to continue to safeguard your personal data adequately. <item>Competent Authorities: We disclose personal data to law enforcement to the extent required by law or strictly necessary for the prevention, detection, or prosecution of criminal acts and fraud, or if we’re legally obliged to do so otherwise. We may need to further disclose personal data to competent authorities to protect and defend our rights or properties, or the rights and properties of our business partners.</item> Business partners: We work with many business partners around the world. These business partners distribute or advertise the Booking.com services, including the services and products of our Trip Providers. When you make a reservation on one of our business partners’ websites or apps, certain personal data that you give them, such as your name and email address, address, payment details, and other relevant info will be forwarded to us to finalize and manage your Trip Reservation. If customer service is provided by the business partner, Booking.com will share relevant reservation details with them (as and when needed) to provide you with appropriate and efficient support. When you make a reservation through one of our business partners’ websites, the business partners can receive certain parts of your personal data related to the specific reservation and your interactions on these partner websites. This is for their commercial purposes. When you make a reservation on a business partner’s website, take the time to read their privacy notice if you’d like to understand how they process your personal data. For fraud detection and prevention purposes, we may also exchange info about our users with business partners, but only when strictly necessary<list><item> Partner Offer: We may enable you to book using Partner Offer, which means your reservation is facilitated by a Trip Provider separate from the booked accommodation. As part of the reservation process, we’ll need to share some relevant personal data with this Trip Provider. If Partner Offer is used, review the info provided in the booking process or check your reservation confirmation for more info about the Trip Provider and how your personal data is further processed by them. </item></list><item>The Booking Holdings Inc. corporate group: Read about how we share your personal data with the Booking Holdings Inc. corporate group .</item> </paragraph>
			<paragraph category="14;14">The transmission of personal data as described in this Privacy Statement may include overseas transfers of personal data to countries whose data protection laws aren’t as comprehensive as those of the countries within the European Union. </paragraph>
			<paragraph category="1.2,10.1,14.2;1.2,10.1,14.2">Where required by European law, we’ll only transfer personal data to recipients that offer an adequate level of data protection. In these situations, as may be required, we make contractual arrangements to ensure that your personal data is still protected in line with European standards. You can ask to see a copy of these contractual agreements by contacting us at dataprotectionoffice@booking.com. </paragraph>
		</segment>
		<segment>
			<title tagname="h3" depth="1" font-size="1.5" font-weight="1.5" category="17;17">How is your personal data shared within the Booking Holdings Inc. corporate group?</title>
			<paragraph category="19;17">Booking.com is part of the Booking Holdings Inc. corporate group. More info is available at Bookingholdings.com . </paragraph>
			<paragraph category="17.1,17.2;17.1,17.2">We may receive personal data about you from other companies in the Booking Holdings Inc. corporate group or share your personal data with them for the following purposes: <item>To provide services (including to make, administer, and manage reservations or handle payments)</item> <item>To provide customer service</item> <item>To detect, prevent, and investigate fraudulence or other illegal activities and data breaches</item> <item>For analytical and product improvement purposes</item> <item>To send you personalized offers or marketing with your consent, or as otherwise permitted by applicable law</item> <item>For hosting, technical support, overall maintenance, and maintaining security of such shared data</item> <item>To ensure compliance with applicable laws</item> </paragraph>
			<paragraph category="10.3,10.6,17;10.3,10.6,17">As applicable and unless indicated otherwise, for purposes A to F, Booking.com relies on its legitimate interest to share and receive personal data. For purpose G, Booking.com relies, where applicable, on compliance with legal obligations (such as legal law enforcement requests). </paragraph>
			<paragraph category="17.2;17.2">For example, Booking.com works closely with Rentalcars.com to offer ground transportation services to customers. Read How is your personal data shared and further processed for ground transportation services? for more info. </paragraph>
			<paragraph category="17.1,17.2;17.1,17.2">All companies within the Booking Holdings Inc. group of companies may need to exchange personal customer data to ensure all users are protected from fraudulent activities on its online platforms. </paragraph>
		</segment>
		<segment>
			<title tagname="h3" depth="1" font-size="1.5" font-weight="1.5" category="17;17">How is your personal data shared and further processed for ground transportation services?</title>
			<paragraph category="17.1,17.2;17.1,17.2">Booking.com and Rentalcars.com (both part of the Booking Holdings Inc. group of companies) work together closely to offer you ground transportation services via Booking.com websites and apps, such as cars.booking.com or taxi.booking.com. </paragraph>
			<paragraph category="17;17">This means that when you're booking or browsing for ground transportation services via the app or website, Booking.com and Rentalcars.com are both responsible for the collection and use of your personal data. </paragraph>
			<paragraph category="1.2;1.2">For more info about the relationship between Booking.com and Rentalcars.com and to exercise your rights regarding your personal data collected by the Booking.com websites and apps, feel free to contact Booking.com anytime. You can do so via the email address listed under Who is responsible for the processing of personal data via Booking.com and how to contact us. </paragraph>
			<paragraph category="17;17">In addition to the data we process jointly to allow you to search for ground transport services and to make your booking, Booking.com and Rentalcars.com will also use your personal data independently for the purposes set out in this Privacy Statement and the Rentalcars.com Privacy Notice . </paragraph>
		</segment>
		<segment>
			<title tagname="h3" depth="1" font-size="1.5" font-weight="1.5" category="11;11">How does Booking.com process communications that you and your booked Trip Provider may send via Booking.com?</title>
			<paragraph category="11;11">Booking.com can offer you and Trip Providers various ways to communicate about the Trip Services and existing Trip Reservations by directing communications via Booking.com. This also allows you and your Trip Provider to contact Booking.com with questions about your Trip Reservation through the website, our apps, and the other channels that we provide. </paragraph>
			<paragraph category="11;11">Booking.com accesses communications and may use automated systems to review, scan, and analyze communications for the following reasons:<list> <item>Security purposes</item> <item>Fraud prevention</item> <item>Compliance with legal and regulatory requirements</item> <item>Investigations of potential misconduct</item> <item>Product development and improvement</item> <item>Research</item> <item>Customer engagement (including to provide you info and offers that we believe might interest you)</item> <item>Customer or technical support</item> </list></paragraph>
			<paragraph category="12;12">We reserve the right to review or block the delivery of communications that we, at our sole discretion, believe might contain malicious content or spam, or pose a risk to you, Trip Providers, Booking.com, or others. </paragraph>
			<paragraph category="16.2;16.2">All communications sent or received using Booking.com communication tools will be received and stored by Booking.com. Business partners (through whose platforms you make a reservation) and Trip Providers might also choose to communicate with you directly by email or other channels that Booking.com doesn’t control. </paragraph>
		</segment>
		<segment>
			<title tagname="h3" depth="1" font-size="1.5" font-weight="1.5" category="11;11">How does Booking.com make use of mobile devices?</title>
			<paragraph category="19;19">We offer free apps for a range of different mobile devices, as well as versions of our regular website that are optimized for browsing on a phone and tablet. </paragraph>
			<paragraph category="11;11">These apps and mobile websites process the personal details you give us in a similar way that our website does. They also allow you to use location services to find Trip Services nearby, if you want. </paragraph>
			<paragraph category="4.1,4.3,11;4.1,4.3,11">With your consent, we may send you push notifications with information about your Trip Reservation. You can also grant us access to your location data or contact details in order to provide services you request. If you upload pictures to our platform, these pictures may include location info (known as metadata) as well. Read your mobile device’s instructions to understand how to change your settings and control the sharing of this type of data. </paragraph>
			<paragraph category="11;11">In order to optimize our services and marketing activities, and to make sure we give you a consistent user experience, we use something known as “cross-device tracking.” This can be done with or without the use of cookies. For more general info about cookies and other similar technologies, see our </paragraph>
			<paragraph category="4.3,4.9,11;4.3,4.9,11"> With cross-device tracking, Booking.com is able to track user behavior across multiple devices. As part of cross-device tracking, we may combine data collected from a particular browser or mobile device with data from another computer or device that’s linked to it. To optimize the content of the Booking.com newsletter, we combine searches and reservations made from different computers and devices. You can unsubscribe from the Booking.com newsletter anytime. Personalized ads shown to you on other websites or in apps, can be offered based on your activities on linked computers and devices. By changing the cookie settings on your device (see our  Cookie statement under “What are your choices?”), you can change your cross-device tracking settings for advertisement purposes. You should know that logging out of your Booking.com account doesn’t mean that you will no longer receive personalized ads. </paragraph>
		</segment>
		<segment>
			<title tagname="h3" depth="1" font-size="1.5" font-weight="1.5" category="11;11">How does Booking.com make use of social media?</title>
			<paragraph category="19;19">At Booking.com, we use social media in different ways. We use it to facilitate the use of online reservation services, to promote our Trip Providers’ travel-related products and services, and to advertise, improve, and facilitate our own services. </paragraph>
			<paragraph category="17.1,17.2;17.1,17.2">The use of social media features can result in the exchange of personal data between Booking.com and the social media service provider, as described below. You’re free to not use any of the social media features available to you.<item> Sign in with your social media account. We offer you the opportunity to sign in to a Booking.com user account with one of your social media accounts. We do this to reduce the need for you to remember different usernames and passwords for different online services. After signing in once, you’ll always be able to use your social media account to sign in to your Booking.com account. You can decouple your Booking.com user account from your chosen social media account anytime you want. </item>Integration of social media plugins: We’ve also integrated social media plugins into Booking.com website and apps. This means that when you click one of the buttons (e.g. Facebook’s “Like” button), certain info is shared with these social media providers. If you’re logged-in to your social media account at the same time, your social media provider may relate this info to your social media account. Depending on your settings, they might also display these actions on your social media profile to others in your network.<item> Other social media services and features. We may integrate other social media services (e.g. social media messaging) for you to interact with Booking.com or your contacts about our services. We may maintain social media accounts and offer apps on several social media sites. Whenever you connect with Booking.com through social media, your social media service provider may allow you to share info with us. If you choose to share, you will generally be told by your social media provider which information will be shared. For example, when you sign in to a Booking.com user account using your social media account, certain info may be shared with Booking.com, including your email address, age, or profile pictures saved to your social media account, depending on what you authorize. </item></paragraph>
			<paragraph category="8,9.1;8,9.1">When you register with a Booking.com social media app or connect to a social media messaging service without a Booking.com user account, the info you choose to share with us may include the basic info available in your social media profile, including your email, status updates, and a list of your contacts. </paragraph>
			<paragraph category="11;11">We’ll use this info to help provide you with the service you requested, for example, to forward a message you want to send to your contacts or to create a personalized user experience on the app or our websites. It means that—if you want us to—we can customize our services to fit your needs, connecting you and your friends to the best travel destinations, as well as analyzing and enhancing our travel-related services. </paragraph>
			<paragraph category="11;11">Your social media provider will be able to tell you more about how they use and process your data when you connect to Booking.com through them. This can include combining the personal data they collect when you use Booking.com through them with info they collect when you use other online platforms also linked to your social media account. </paragraph>
			<paragraph category="4.1;4.1">If you decide to connect using your Facebook or Google account, review the following links for info about how these parties use data they receive: Facebook and Google. </paragraph>
		</segment>	
		<segment>
			<title tagname="h3" depth="1" font-size="1.5" font-weight="1.5" category="12;12">What security and retention procedures does Booking.com put in place to safeguard your personal data?</title>
			<paragraph category="12;12">We observe reasonable procedures to prevent unauthorized access to and the misuse of personal data. </paragraph>
			<paragraph category="12;12">We use appropriate business systems and procedures to protect and safeguard the personal data you give us. We also use security procedures and technical and physical restrictions for accessing and using the personal data on our servers. Only authorized personnel are allowed to access personal data in the course of their work. </paragraph>
			<paragraph category="12,16.1;12,16.1">We’ll keep your personal data for as long as we think necessary to enable you to use our services or to provide our services to you (including maintaining your Booking.com user account, if you have one), to comply with applicable laws, to resolve any disputes, and to otherwise allow us to conduct our business, including to detect and prevent fraud or other illegal activities. All personal data we keep about you is covered by this Privacy Statement. </paragraph>
			<paragraph category="12,4.3;12,4.3">For added protection, westrongly recommend setting up two-factor authentication for your Booking.com account. This adds an extra authentication step to make sure anyone who gets ahold of your username and password (e.g. through phishing or social engineering) won’t be able to access your account. You can set this up in the Security section of your account settings. </paragraph>
		</segment>
		<segment>
			<title tagname="h3" depth="1" font-size="1.5" font-weight="1.5" category="15;15">How does Booking.com treat personal data belonging to children?</title>
			<paragraph category="15;15">Our services aren’t intended for children under 16, and we’ll never collect their data unless it’s provided by (and with the consent of) a parent or guardian. The limited cases we might need to collect data for include as part of a reservation, the purchase of other travel-related services, or in other exceptional circumstances, such as features addressed to families. Again, this will only be used and collected as provided by a parent or guardian and with their consent. </paragraph>
			<paragraph category="16.3,15;16.3,15">If we find out that we processed info of a child under 16 without the valid consent of a parent or guardian, we reserve the right to delete it. </paragraph>
		</segment>
		<segment>
			<title tagname="h3" depth="1" font-size="1.5" font-weight="1.5" category="4;4">How can you control the personal data you’ve given to Booking.com?</title>
			<paragraph category="4.2,4.3,4.4,4.5,4.6,4.9,10.2,10.3;4.2,4.3,4.4,4.5,4.6,4.9,10.2,10.3">We want you to be in control of how your personal data is used by us. You can do this in the following ways: <item>You can ask us for a copy of the personal data we hold about you.</item> <item>You can inform us of any changes to your personal data or ask us to correct any of the personal data we hold about you. As explained below, you can make some of these changes yourself when you have a user account.</item> <item>In certain situations, you can ask us to erase, block, or restrict the processing of the personal data we hold about you, or object to particular ways that we use your personal data.</item> <item>In certain situations, you can also ask us to send the personal data you've given us to a third party.</item> <item>Where we use your personal data on the basis of your consent, you’re entitled to withdraw that consent at any time, subject to applicable law.</item> <item>Where we process your personal data based on legitimate interest or the public interest, you have the right to object to that use of your personal data at any time, subject to applicable law.</item> </paragraph>
			<paragraph category="4.3;4.3">We rely on you to make sure that your personal info is complete, accurate, and current. Let us know about any changes to or inaccuracies in your personal info as soon as possible. </paragraph>
			<paragraph category="4.2,4.3,4.4;4.2,4.3,4.4">If you have a Booking.com user account, you can access a lot of your personal data through our website or apps. You’ll generally find the option to add, update, or remove info we have about you in your account settings. </paragraph>
			<paragraph category="4.2;4.2">If any of the personal data we have about you isn’t accessible through our website or apps, you can send us a request, which won’t cost you anything. </paragraph>
			<paragraph category="3.2,4.2,4.4,7;3.2,4.2,4.4,7">If you want to exercise your right of access or erasure, all you need to do is complete and submit the Data Subject Request for Booking.com Customers form. For any requests relating to this Privacy Statement, to exercise any of your other rights, or if you have a complaint, contact our Data Protection Officer at dataprotectionoffice@booking.com . You can also contact your local data protection authority. </paragraph>
			<paragraph category="4.6,10.3;4.6,10.3">If you want to object to your personal data being processed on the basis of legitimate interest and there’s no option to opt out directly, contact us at dataprotectionoffice@booking.com . </paragraph>
		</segment>
		<segment>
			<title tagname="h3" depth="1" font-size="1.5" font-weight="1.5" category="1.2;1.2">Who is responsible for the processing of personal data via Booking.com and how to contact us?</title>
			<paragraph category="1.1;1.1">Booking.com B.V. controls the processing of personal data as described in this Privacy Statement, except where explicitly stated otherwise. Booking.com B.V. is a private limited liability company incorporated under the laws of the Netherlands and has its offices at Herengracht 597, 1017 CE Amsterdam, the Netherlands. </paragraph>
			<paragraph category="3.2;3.2">If you have any questions about this Privacy Statement or our processing of your personal data, contact our Data Protection Officer at dataprotectionoffice@booking.com and we’ll get back to you as soon as possible. </paragraph>
			<paragraph category="1.2;1.2">For questions about a reservation, contact our customer service team through the customer service contact page . </paragraph>
			<paragraph category="19;19">Requests from law enforcement should be submitted using the Law Enforcement process. </paragraph>
			<segment>
				<title tagname="h4" depth="1" font-size="1.25" font-weight="1.25" category="19;19">Country-specific provisions</title>
				<paragraph category="19;19">Depending on the law that applies to you, we may be required to provide some additional info. Review the list below to find any additional info relevant to your situation. </paragraph>
			</segment>
		</segment>
		<segment>
			<title tagname="h3" depth="1" font-size="1.5" font-weight="1.5" category="18.2;18.2">For California residents – California law</title>
			<paragraph category="18.2;18.2">This section supplements our Privacy Statement and only applies if you live in the state of California. Where applicable, it describes how we use and process your personal info (the term used under the law) and explains your particular rights under California law. </paragraph>
			<paragraph category="18.2;18.2">We describe below the personal information we collect about you, including by identifying specific categories of information: <item>Identifiers (e.g., your name, account number, email address, <item>IP address</item>)</item> <item>Financial, medical, or health insurance information (e.g., your bank account number, payment card number, medical information if provided by you or on your behalf)</item> <item>Characteristics of protected classifications under California or federal law (e.g. your gender, religion, sexual orientation)</item> <item>Commercial information (e.g., your purchase information)</item> <item>Internet or other electronic network activity information (e.g., information about your website or app usage)</item> <item>Geolocation data (e.g., your physical location)</item> <item>Visual information (e.g., any photographs you upload on your account)</item> <item>Inferences (e.g., analytics and preferences)</item> <item>Professional or employment-related information (e.g., employer and business travel details)</item> </paragraph>
			<paragraph category="4.1;18.2">If you want more info about the categories of sources from which we obtain personal info, the specific types of personal info we collect, or the purposes for which we collect them, read the sections of our Privacy Statement titled “What kind of personal data does Booking.com collect?” and “Why does Booking.com collect and use your personal data?” </paragraph>
			<paragraph category="4.1;18.2">To learn more about the receipt of personal info from and the sharing of personal info with business partners, read the sections “What kind of personal data does Booking.com collect?” and “How does Booking.com share your data with third parties?” </paragraph>
			<paragraph category="18.2;18.2">We may share certain parts of your personal info with third parties, which under Californian law can be treated as a "sale" of information. This may include info related to Identifiers, Commercial information, Geolocation data, Internet activity, and Inferences, as described above. We may also share your personal info listed above in A–I for “business purposes,” such as to service providers who assist us with securing our services, for payment purposes, customer support services, delivering marketing messages, or advertisements. For more details, including the recipients of your personal info, check out the “What kind of personal data does Booking.com collect?” and “How does Booking.com share your data with third parties?” sections of our Privacy Statement. </paragraph>
			<paragraph category="18.2;18.2">California law provides you with certain rights, including the right to access specific pieces of personal info, to learn about how we process personal info including disclosure or sale of personal info, to request deletion of personal info, to opt out of “sales,” and to not be denied goods or services for exercising these rights. </paragraph>
			<paragraph category="4.9;18.2">You may exercise your right to opt out of “sales” by clicking on this link and following the instructions: https://www.booking.com/content/ccpa.html </paragraph>
			<paragraph category="18.2;18.2">To exercise your right to request access to or the deletion of your personal info under California law, fill out our Data Subject Request for Booking.com Customers form . To otherwise exercise these or any of your other rights under California law, or to contact us with questions and concerns about this privacy notice and our practices, contact us at dataprotectionoffice@booking.com with the subject line: “California Resident Privacy Rights – Request.” </paragraph>
			<paragraph category="18.2;18.2">If you’re an authorized agent seeking to exercise rights on behalf of a California consumer, contact us at the email above and attach a copy of the consumer’s written authorization designating you as their agent. We may need to verify your identity before completing your rights request by, for example, requesting info about your previous Trip Reservations with us. </paragraph>
			<paragraph category="18.2;18.2">Booking.com’s services are not directed at children under the age of 16. Therefore, Booking.com doesn’t knowingly sell the personal info of minors under the age of 16 years without appropriate consent, as required under the California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA). </paragraph>
			<paragraph category="18.2;18.2">Booking.com has compiled the following statistics about the receipt and handling of requests identified as being submitted under the CCPA by consumers from California, for the period between January 1, 2020 and December 31, 2020:<list> <item>Number of "requests to know" Booking.com received, complied with (wholly or in part), or denied: 27</item> <item>Number of "requests to delete" Booking.com received, complied with (wholly or in part), or denied: 136</item> <item>Number of "requests to opt out of sales" that Booking.com complied with (wholly or in part), or denied: 13,866</item> <item>Average number of days taken by Booking.com to substantially respond to requests to know, delete, or opt out: 8.514</item> </list></paragraph>
		</segment>
		<segment>
			<title tagname="h3" depth="1" font-size="1.5" font-weight="1.5" category="18.2;18.2">South Korea</title>
			<paragraph category="1.2,2.1;18.2">Customers from South Korea may also use the contact details set out below for requests related to this privacy statement: Pursuant to the Act on the Promotion of the Use of the Information Network and Information Protection, the info regarding the domestic agent is as follows: Name and representative: Booking.com Korea Limited (Representative: Su Yeon Kim) Address, telephone number, and email address: 17F Gran Seoul, 33 Jongro, Jongro-Gu, Seoul, South Korea, +82 2 6323 8008, privacy.kr@booking.com. </paragraph>
		</segment>
		<segment>
			<title tagname="h3" depth="1" font-size="1.5" font-weight="1.5" category="18.2;18.2">Turkey</title>
			<paragraph category="1.2,2.1;18.2">Customers from Turkey may also use the contact details set out below for requests related to this privacy statement: The local representative for Booking.com B.V. in Turkey is Ozdagistanli Ekici Avukatlık Ortaklığı, located at Al Zambak Sok No: 2 Varyap Meridian Grand Tower A Blok K: 32 D: 270 Ataşehir-İstanbul. </paragraph>
			</segment>
		</segment>
	
</policy>