<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<policy>
	<url>https://www.  .com</url>
	<update_time>20/ /</update_time>
	<download_time>2021/02/18</download_time>
	<paragraph>Posted: 01 April 2019. Previous version Gumtree.com Limited ("Gumtree", "we" or "us" or "our"), 100 New Bridge Street, London, EC4V 6JA, registered in England and Wales with number 3934849 is the data controller and operator of Gumtree.com. Gumtree is committed to your privacy. This privacy notice explains our collection, use, disclosure, retention, and protection of your personal information. </paragraph>
	<segment>
		<title tagname="h2" depth="2" font-size="1.12" font-weight="1.75" category="">Scope</title>
		<paragraph>This privacy notice applies to any Gumtree website, application, service, or tool (collectively "Services") where this privacy notice is referenced, regardless of how you access or use them, including through mobile devices. You are contracting with Gumtree (the data controller) who is responsible for the collection, use, disclosure, retention and protection of your personal information in accordance with our privacy standards, this privacy notice, as well as any applicable national laws. Gumtree may transfer data to other members of the Gumtree corporate group , as described in this privacy notice. We may amend this privacy notice at any time by posting the amended version on this site including the effective date of the amended version. Return to Summary on Scope </paragraph>
	</segment>
	<segment>
		<title tagname="h2" depth="2" font-size="1.12" font-weight="1.75" category="8,9;8,9">Personal Information We Collect</title>
		<segment>
			<title tagname="h4" depth="3" font-size="0.94" font-weight="1.75" category="8;8">What is Personal Information?</title>
			<paragraph category="8;8">Personal Information is information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person. An identifiable natural person is one who can be identified, directly or indirectly, by reference to an identifier such as a name, an identification number, location data, an online identifier, or to one or more factors specific to the physical, physiological, genetic, mental, economic, cultural or social identity of that natural person. </paragraph>
			<paragraph category="8;8">We do not consider personal information to include information that has been anonymized or aggregated so that it can no longer be used to identify a specific natural person, whether in combination with other information or otherwise. </paragraph>
			<paragraph category="8,9;8,9">We collect personal information from you when you use our Services. </paragraph>
			<paragraph category="8,9.1,9.2;8,9.1,9.2">We collect personal information from you and any devices (including mobile devices) you use when you: use our Services, register for an account with us, provide us information on a web form, update or add information to your account, participate in community discussions, chats, or dispute resolution or when you otherwise correspond with us. </paragraph>
			<paragraph category="8,9.1,11;8,9.1,11">Some of this personal information, such as a way to identify you, is necessary to enter into our Terms of Use . The provision of all other personal information is voluntary, but may be necessary in order to use our Services, such as the offer details or contact information needed to post an ad. </paragraph>
			<paragraph category="8,9.3;8,9.3">We may also collect personal information from other sources, as described below. </paragraph>
		</segment>
		<segment>
			<title tagname="h4" depth="3" font-size="0.94" font-weight="1.75" category="8,9.1;8,9.1">Personal information you give us when you use our Services or register for an account with us</title>
			<paragraph category="8,9.1;8,9.1">Identifying information such as your name, addresses, telephone numbers or email addresses when you register for an account with us.<item> Information you provide when posting an ad, responding to an ad or other transaction-based content that you generate or that is connected to your account as a result of a transaction you are involved in. </item>Other content that you generate, or that is connected to your account and your use of our Services such as your use of the following website functions: My Gumtree (Manage my ads, Messages, Favourites, Saved Searches, My Favourites, My Details, Create Account, Ratings and Reviews) or the Help section.<item> Financial information (such as credit card or bank account numbers) in connection with a transaction. </item>In some instances, when you use our Services, you may provide age, gender, interests and favorites.<item> You may also provide us other information through a web form, by updating or adding information to your account, through your participation in community discussions, chats, dispute resolution, or when you otherwise communicate with us regarding our Services. </item>Additional information we are required or authorized by applicable national laws to collect and process in order to authenticate or identify you or to verify the information we have collected. </paragraph>
		</segment>
		<segment>
			<title tagname="h4" depth="3" font-size="0.94" font-weight="1.75" category="8,9.2;8,9.2">Personal information we collect automatically when you use our Services or register for an account with us</title>
			<paragraph category="8,9.2;8,9.2">We collect information about your interaction with our Services, your advertising preferences, and your communications with us. This is information we receive from devices (including mobile devices) you use when you access our Services. This information could include the following: Device ID or unique identifier, device type, ID for advertising, and unique device token.<item> Location information, including location information from your mobile device. Keep in mind that most mobile devices allow you to control or disable the use of location services by any application on your mobile device in the device's settings menu. </item>Computer and connection information such as statistics on your page views, traffic to and from the sites, referral URL, ad data, your IP address, your browsing history, and your web log information. </paragraph>
		</segment>
		<segment>
			<title tagname="h4" depth="3" font-size="0.94" font-weight="1.75" category="8,9.2;8,9.2">Personal information we collect using cookies and similar technologies</title>
			<paragraph category="8,9.2;8,9.2">We use cookies, web beacons, unique identifiers, and similar technologies to collect information about the pages you view, the links you click, and other actions you take when using our Services, within our advertising or email content.<item> For more information about our use of these technologies, and how to control them, see our User Cookie Notice . </item></paragraph>
		</segment>
		<segment>
			<title tagname="h4" depth="3" font-size="0.94" font-weight="1.75" category="8,9.3;8,9.3">Personal information collected from other sources</title>
			<paragraph category="8,9.3;8,9.3">We supplement the personal information we collect directly with information collected from third parties and add it to your account information. For example, we collect and use demographic and other information that is publically available in an applicable jurisdiction, additional contact information, credit check information, and information from credit bureaus, as allowed by applicable national laws.<item> Social Media. We allow you to share information with social media sites, or use social media sites to create your account or to connect your account with the respective social media site. Those social media sites may give us automatic access to certain personal information retained by them about you (e.g., content viewed by you, content liked by you, and information about the advertisements you have been shown or have clicked on, etc.). You control the personal information you allow us to have access to through the privacy settings on the applicable social media site and the permissions you give us when you grant us access to the personal information retained by the respective social media site about you. By associating an account managed by a social media site with your account and authorizing us to have access to this information, you agree that we can collect, use and retain the information provided by these social media sites in accordance with this privacy notice. We may also use plug-ins or other technologies from various social media sites. If you click on a link provided via a social media plug-in, you are voluntarily establishing a connection with that respective social media site. </item>If you give us personal information about someone else, you must do so only with that person’s authorization. You should inform them how we collect, use, disclose, and retain their personal information according to our privacy notice. Return to Summary on Personal Information We Collect </paragraph>
		</segment>
	</segment>
	<segment>
		<title tagname="h2" depth="2" font-size="1.12" font-weight="1.75" category="11;11">How we use your Personal Information</title>
		<paragraph category="11;11">We use your personal information to provide and improve our Services, provide you with a personalized experience on our sites, contact you about your account and our Services, provide you customer service, provide you with personalized advertising and marketing, and to detect, prevent, mitigate and investigate fraudulent or illegal activities. </paragraph>
		<paragraph category="10,11;10,11">We use the personal information we collect from you for a range of different business purposes and according to different legal bases of processing. The following is a summary of how and according to which legal bases we use your personal information. </paragraph>
		<segment>
			<title tagname="h4" depth="3" font-size="0.94" font-weight="1.75" category="10.1,10.2,10.4,10.6,11;10.1,10.2,10.4,10.6,11">We use your personal information to fulfill an agreement with you and provide you with our Services, to comply with our legal obligation, protect your vital interest, or as may be required for the public good. This includes:</title>
			<paragraph category="11;11">To provide access to and use of our Services (especially, to allow you to post and manage ads or other content), account management, operate, measure and improve our Services, keep our Services safe, secure and operational, and customize site content that includes items and services that you may like in response to actions that you take.<item> To give you access to your internal messages and other features. </item>To contact you regarding your account, to troubleshoot problems with your account, to resolve a dispute, to collect fees or monies owed, or as otherwise necessary to provide you customer service.<list> When contacting you for such purposes as outlined above, we may contact you via email, telephone, SMS/text messages, postal mail, and via mobile push notifications. </list>To provide other services requested by you as described when we collect the information, including displaying a location with your ad via Google Maps (for more information see the Google Privacy Notice ).<item> We use general location information to provide you with location based services (such as advertising, search results, and other personalized content). </item>To prevent, detect, mitigate, and investigate fraud, security breaches or other potentially prohibited or illegal activities.<item> To enforce our Terms of Use , this privacy notice, or other policies, applicable national laws, and any agreement we may have with you. </item></paragraph>
		</segment>
		<segment>
			<title tagname="h4" depth="3" font-size="0.94" font-weight="1.75" category="10.3,11;10.3,11">We use your personal information to pursue our legitimate interests where your rights and freedoms do not outweigh these interests. We have implemented controls to balance our interests with your rights. This includes to:</title>
			<paragraph category="11;11">Improve our Services, for example by reviewing information associated with stalled or crashed pages experienced by users allowing us to identify and fix problems and give you a better experience.<item> Personalize, measure, and improve our advertising based on your advertising customization preferences. </item>Contact you via email, postal mail or telephone in order to offer you coupons, discounts and special promotions, poll your opinions through surveys or questionnaires and inform you about our Services, as authorized by applicable law.<item> Contact you about public policy matters, or other current events, related to your ability to use our Services. This could include an invitation to join a petition, letter writing, call or other sort of public policy related campaigns. </item>Deliver targeted marketing, service updates, and promotional offers based on your communication preferences.<item> Measure the performance of our email marketing campaigns (e.g. by analyzing open and click rates). </item>Monitor and improve the information security of our site and mobile applications. </paragraph>
		</segment>
		<segment>
			<title tagname="h4" depth="3" font-size="0.94" font-weight="1.75" category="10.5,11;10.5,11">With your consent, we may use your personal information to:</title>
			<paragraph category="11;11">Provide you with marketing via telephone calls, email, SMS or text.<item> Provide you with marketing from other corporate group companies. </item>Provide you with marketing from third parties.<item> Customize third party advertising you might see on third party websites. </item>Use your precise geo-location to provide location based services. </paragraph>
			<paragraph category="4.9;4.9">You have the right to withdraw your consent at any time. </paragraph>
			<paragraph category="10.5,11;10.5,11">We may use technologies considered automated decision making or profiling. We will not make automated-decisions about you that would significantly affect you, unless such a decision is necessary as part of a contract we have with you, we have your consent, or we are required by law to use such technology. Return to Summary on How we use your Personal Information </paragraph>
		</segment>
	</segment>
	<segment>
		<title tagname="h2" depth="2" font-size="1.12" font-weight="1.75" category="6;6">Your choices about how we use your personal information</title>
		<paragraph category="6;6">You have choices about how we use your personal information to communicate with you, to send you marketing information, how we provide you with customized and relevant advertising, and whether you want to stay signed into your account. Learn more on Your choices about how we use your personal information </paragraph>
	</segment>
	<segment>
		<title tagname="h2" depth="2" font-size="1.12" font-weight="1.75" category="4.2,4.3;4.2,4.3">Ways you can access, control, and correct your personal information</title>
		<paragraph category="4.2,4.3,4.4,4.5;4.2,4.3,4.4,4.4,4.5">We respect your right to access, correct, request deletion or request restriction of our usage of your personal information as required by applicable law. We also take steps to ensure that the personal information we collect is accurate and up to date.<list><item> You have the right to know what personal information we maintain about you </item>We will provide you with a copy of your personal information in a structured, commonly used and machine readable format on request<item> If your personal information is incorrect or incomplete, you have the right to ask us to update it </item>You have the right to object to our processing of your personal information<item> You can also ask us to delete or restrict how we use your personal information, but this right is determined by applicable law and may impact your access to some of our Services </item></list>Learn more on Ways you can access, control, and correct your personal information </paragraph>
	</segment>
	<segment>
		<title tagname="h2" depth="2" font-size="1.12" font-weight="1.75" category="17;17">How we might share your personal information</title>
		<paragraph category="17.1,17.2,10.6;17.1,17.2,10.6">We may disclose your personal information to other members of the Gumtree corporate group or to third parties. This disclosure may be required for us to provide you access to our Services, to comply with our legal obligations, to enforce our Terms of Use, to facilitate our marketing and advertising activities, or to prevent, detect, mitigate, and investigate fraudulent or illegal activities related to our Services. We attempt to minimize the amount of personal information we disclose to what is directly relevant and necessary to accomplish the specified purpose. We do not sell, rent, or otherwise disclose your personal information to third parties for their marketing and advertising purposes without your consent. </paragraph>
		<paragraph category="17.1,17.2;17.1,17.2">We may disclose your personal information to the following parties for the following purposes: Corporate group members , who may use it to:<list><item> Provide joint content and services (like registration, transactions, and customer support) </item>Help detect, investigate, mitigate and prevent potentially fraudulent and illegal acts, violations of our Terms of Use , and data security breaches<item> Provide you personalized advertising </item>Improve their products, sites, applications, services, tools, and marketing communications.<item> Members of our corporate group will use your personal information to send you marketing communications only if you have consented to receive such communications from them or if otherwise permitted by the law. </item></list></paragraph>
		<segment>
			<title tagname="h4" depth="3" font-size="0.94" font-weight="1.75" category="19;17.1">Service Providers and financial institutions partners as follows:</title>
			<paragraph category="17.1,17.2;17.1,17.2">Third party service providers who help us to provide our Services, payment processing services, assist us in providing customize advertising, to assist us with the prevention, detection, mitigation, and investigation of potentially illegal acts, violations of our Terms of Use , fraud and/or security breaches, bill collection, affiliate and rewards programs and other business operations.<item> Third party financial institutions with whom we partner to offer financial products to you, for them to provide joint content and services (such as, registration, transactions and customer support). These third party financial institution partners will use your personal information to send you marketing communications only if you have requested their services. </item></paragraph>
		</segment>
		<segment>
			<title tagname="h4" depth="3" font-size="0.94" font-weight="1.75" category="19;17.1">Third party providers of websites, applications, services and tools and corporate group members:</title>
			<paragraph category="17.1,17.2;17.1,17.2">With whom we partner so that they can publish or advertise your listings and their content on their websites or in their applications, services and tools. If we transfer personal information along with the content of your listings to third party providers, this will be solely on the basis of an agreement limiting use by the third party provider of such personal information to processing necessary to fulfil their contract with us and obligating the third party provider to take security measures with regard to such data. Third party providers are not permitted to sell, lease or in any other way transfer the personal information included in your listings to third parties. </paragraph>
		</segment>
		<segment>
			<title tagname="h4" depth="3" font-size="0.94" font-weight="1.75" category="19;17.2">Law enforcement, legal proceedings, and as authorized by law</title>
			<paragraph category="17.1,17.2,10.6;17.1,17.2,10.6">To comply with our legal requirements, enforce our Terms of Use , respond to claims that a listing or other content violates the rights of others, or protect anyone's rights, property or safety.<item> To law enforcement or governmental agencies, or authorized third-parties, in response to a verified request or legal process relating to a criminal investigation or alleged or suspected illegal activity or any other activity that exposes us, you, or any other of our users to legal liability. We will only disclose information we deem relevant to the investigation or inquiry, such as name, city, state, postcode, telephone number, email address, User ID history, device ID, IP address, fraud complaints, offers and listing history. </item>To participants of Gumtree’s Brand Infringement NTD Program under confidentiality agreement, as we in our sole discretion deem necessary or appropriate in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringement, piracy, or other unlawful activity. In such events, we will disclose seller’s name, street address, city, postcode, country, phone number, email address and company name to the participants of Gumtree’s Brand Infringement NTD Program .<item> To credit agencies or bureaus as authorized by applicable national laws (e.g. information on late or missed payments or other defaults on your account that may be reflected in your credit report or file). </item>To third parties involved in a legal proceeding, if they provide us with a subpoena, court order or substantially similar legal basis, or we otherwise believe in good faith that the disclosure of information is necessary to prevent imminent physical harm or financial loss or to report suspected illegal activity. </paragraph>
		</segment>
		<segment>
			<title tagname="h4" depth="3" font-size="0.94" font-weight="1.75" category="19;17.2">Change of Ownership</title>
			<paragraph category="17.2;17.2">If we are subject to a merger or acquisition with/by another company, we may share information with them in accordance with our global privacy standards. Should such an event occur, we will require that the new combined entity follow this privacy notice with respect to your personal information. If we intend to handle your personal information for any purposes not covered in this privacy notice, you will receive prior notification of the processing of your personal information for the new purposes. </paragraph>
		</segment>
		<segment>
			<title tagname="h4" depth="3" font-size="0.94" font-weight="1.75" category="14;14,17.2">International Data Transfers</title>
			<paragraph category="14.2;14.2,17.2">We will only transfer your personal data to third countries, i.e. countries outside the EEA and the UK, on the basis of appropriate safeguards. We provide the necessary safeguards, e.g. through the conclusion of standard data protection clauses (2010/87/EU, 2001/497/EC or 2004/915/EC) with the recipients, or through other measures provided for by law. A copy of the documentation of the measures taken by us is available on request. Return to Summary on How we might share your personal information </paragraph>
		</segment>
	</segment>
	<segment>
		<title tagname="h2" depth="2" font-size="1.12" font-weight="1.75" category="16.1;16.1">How long we keep your personal information</title>
		<paragraph category="16.1;16.1">We retain your personal information for as long as necessary to provide the Services you have requested, or for other essential purposes such as complying with our legal obligations, resolving disputes, and enforcing our policies. </paragraph>
		<paragraph category="16.1;16.1">Our specific retention times for personal information are documented in our records retention schedules. How long we retain personal information can vary significantly based on context of the Services we provide and on our legal obligations. The following factors typically influence retention periods:<list><item> How long is the personal information needed to provide our Services? This includes such things as maintaining and improving the performance of our products, keeping our systems secure, and maintaining appropriate business and financial records. This is the general rule that establishes the baseline for most of our data retention periods. </item>Is the personal information sensitive? If so, a shortened retention time is generally appropriate.<item> Have you provided consent for a longer retention period? If so, we will retain data in accordance with your consent. </item>Are we subject to a legal, contractual, or similar obligation to retain your personal information? Examples can include mandatory data retention laws in the applicable jurisdiction, government orders to preserve data relevant to an investigation, or personal information retained for the purposes of litigation. </list></paragraph>
		<paragraph category="16.3;16.3">After it is no longer necessary for us to retain your personal information, we will dispose of it in a secure manner according to our data retention and deletion policies. Return to Summary on How long we keep your personal information </paragraph>
	</segment>
	<segment>
		<title tagname="h2" depth="2" font-size="1.12" font-weight="1.75" category="18.1;18.1">Cookies &amp; Similar Technologies</title>
		<paragraph category="18.1;18.1">When you visit or interact with our sites, services, applications, tools or messaging, we or our authorized service providers may use cookies and other similar technologies to help provide you with a better, faster, and safer experience, and for advertising and marketing purposes. You can read our full User Cookie Notice for more information. </paragraph>
	</segment>
	<segment>
		<title tagname="h2" depth="2" font-size="1.12" font-weight="1.75" category="12;12">How do we protect your Personal Information</title>
		<paragraph category="12;12">We protect your personal information using technical and administrative security measures to reduce the risks of loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure and alteration. Some of the safeguards we use are firewalls and data encryption, physical access controls to our data centers, and information access authorization controls. For more information about staying safe on Gumtree, or to report an issue with your account please visit our Safety Advice page.If you believe your account has been abused, please contact Customer Support . </paragraph>
	</segment>
	<segment>
		<title tagname="h2" depth="2" font-size="1.12" font-weight="1.75" category="19;19">Other important Privacy Information</title>
		<paragraph category="19;19">This section describes some additional privacy information related to your use of our Services that you may find important. </paragraph>
		<segment>
			<title tagname="h4" depth="3" font-size="0.94" font-weight="1.75" category="19;19">When you share your personal information on our sites or applications – what happens?</title>
			<paragraph category="19;19">Other users have access to the information you share on Gumtree. For example, other users can see your ratings, reviews and associated comments. Other users can also see any information you chose to share in your profile. </paragraph>
			<paragraph category="19;19">When you use our Services, your public user ID may be displayed and available to the public and associated with all of your public Gumtree activity. Notices sent to other users about suspicious activity and notice violations on our sites may refer to your public user ID and specific items. If you associate your name with your user ID, the people to whom you have revealed your name may then be able to identify your Gumtree activities. </paragraph>
		</segment>
		<segment>
			<title tagname="h4" depth="3" font-size="0.94" font-weight="1.75" category="19;19">Your responsibilities over information you receive on Gumtree</title>
			<paragraph category="1.1;1.1">When you correspond with another user and receive personal information of the other user (such as their name, email address, contact details, shipping and billing address) you are, independent from us, the controller of such data and you must comply with the applicable privacy laws. </paragraph>
			<paragraph category="4.2;4.2">You may use the personal information that you have access to only for Gumtree transaction-related purposes, or for other services offered through Gumtree (such as fraud complaints, and member-to-member communications), and for purposes expressly consented by the user to whom the information relates. Using personal information of other users that you have access to for any other purpose constitutes a violation of our Terms of Use . </paragraph>
		</segment>
		<segment>
			<title tagname="h4" depth="3" font-size="0.94" font-weight="1.75" category="19;19">Unwanted or threatening email</title>
			<paragraph category="10.5;10.5">We do not tolerate abuse of our Services. You do not have permission to add other users to your mailing list (email or postal), call, or send him/her text messages for commercial purposes, even if this user purchased something from you, unless the user has given his/her explicit consent. Sending unwanted or threatening email and text messages is against our Terms of Use . To report Gumtree-related spam or spoof emails please notify us here . </paragraph>
		</segment>
		<segment>
			<title tagname="h4" depth="3" font-size="0.94" font-weight="1.75" category="19;19">Communication tools</title>
			<paragraph category="19;19">We may scan messages automatically and check for spam, viruses, phishing and other malicious activity, illegal or prohibited content or violations of our Terms of Use, this privacy notice or our other policies. </paragraph>
		</segment>
		<segment>
			<title tagname="h4" depth="3" font-size="0.94" font-weight="1.75" category="15;15">Children's Privacy</title>
			<paragraph category="15;15">Our websites are general audience websites and not intended for children. We do not knowingly collect personal information from users deemed to be children under their respective national laws. </paragraph>
		</segment>
		<segment>
			<title tagname="h4" depth="3" font-size="0.94" font-weight="1.75" category="19;19">Third Party Privacy Practices</title>
			<paragraph category="19;19">This privacy notice addresses only our use and handling of personal information we collect from you in connection with providing you our Services. If you disclose your information to a third party, or visit a third party website via a link from our Services, their privacy notices and practices will apply to any personal information you provide to them or they collect from you. </paragraph>
			<paragraph category="12;12">We cannot guarantee the privacy or security of your personal information once you provide it to a third party and we encourage you to evaluate the privacy and security policies of your trading partner before entering into a transaction and choosing to share your personal information. This is true even where the third parties to whom you disclose personal information are bidders, buyers or sellers on our site. Return to Summary on Other important Privacy Information </paragraph>
		</segment>
	</segment>
	<segment>
		<title tagname="h2" depth="2" font-size="1.12" font-weight="1.75" category="1.2;1.2">Contact Us</title>
		<paragraph category="1.2,7;1.2,7">If you have a question or a complaint about this privacy notice, our global privacy standards, or our information handling practices, you can contact us here . </paragraph>
		<paragraph category="3.2;3.2">You can also email us at dpo@gumtree.com or reach us and our data protection officer in writing at: 100 New Bridge Street, London EC4V 6JA. </paragraph>
		<paragraph category="7;7">Your right to file complaints with a data protection supervisory authority remains unaffected. </paragraph>
	</segment>
</policy>