<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<policy>
	<segment>
		<title category="" tagname="strong" depth="4" font-size="0.94" font-weight="1.75">
			DEFINITIONS</title>
		<paragraph category="">1. KG Media / We / Us / Our means Kompas Gramedia Group of Media which is engaged in various media business fields, such as Television, Radio, Printing, Digital and other media business areas. </paragraph>
		<paragraph category="">2.  Affiliate / affiliates / affiliate / affiliates  means a subsidiary of and / or parties under the control of Kompas Gramedia Group of Media and / or Kompas Gramedia Group. </paragraph>
		<paragraph category="">3. Service / Services / service / services means any services and / or products and / or other activities or services in whatever form we provide / organize whether we provide / administer through the Portal or without going through the Portal (such as events and etc). </paragraph>
		<paragraph category="">4. Portal / portal means every software application and / or every website and / or any other form of digital platform both already existing and will be in the future, which We and / or our Affiliates develop and operate so that our Services can be accessed by You.</paragraph>
		<paragraph category=""> 5. Customer / User / You / Yourself is any party who uses and / or accesses and / or participates in our services, whether through the Portal or not through the Portal, and whether registered on the Portal or not registered on the Portal. </paragraph>
		<paragraph category="">6. Personal Data / personal data / Data / data means data or information about yourself that we obtain through the use / interaction of the Portal and / or services by you, both which can be personally identified and which have not been personally identified including but not limited to such as name, address, date of birth, place of birth, your job, place of work, personal identity, other identifying documents, telephone number, e-mail address and other information that can identify you as a user. </paragraph>
		<paragraph category="">7. Terms of Use means standard operating procedures or other provisions relating to access / use of any Portal or Services provided by Us and / or its Affiliates, which can be changed and updated from time to time by Us and / or Affiliates. </paragraph>
	</segment>
	<segment>
		<title category="" tagname="strong" depth="4" font-size="0.94" font-weight="1.75">
			SCOPE</title>
		<paragraph>This Privacy Policy applies to all Personal Data across Our Services and / or our business partners (vendors, partners and other stakeholders). Please see various products and subsidiaries that are Affiliates of us here: </paragraph>
		<paragraph>(1) https://www.kompasgramedia.com/business/media or </paragraph>
		<paragraph>(2) https://www.kgmedia.id/ </paragraph>
		<paragraph>Every addition to a product / service that will come in the future is a product / service that is recognized by us, then automatically follows this Privacy Policy. In this case, we are not obliged to show our company documents, but we can show a document which states that each product or service is correct, including our services. </paragraph>
	</segment>
	<segment>
		<title tagname="strong" depth="4" font-size="0.94" font-weight="1.75" category="8,9,11;8,9,11">
			PURPOSE OF COLLECTION AND USE OF PERSONAL DATA</title>
		<paragraph category="11;11">We use and provide your Personal Data, including but not limited to Affiliates, for the following purposes: </paragraph>
		<paragraph category="11;11">1. To provide support or other information;</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="11;11">We may use your Personal Data to provide support or other information related to the history of use that has been carried out by the Customer, including but not limited to such as Customer complaints, Customer calls, Customer confirmations related to our services. </paragraph>
		<paragraph category="11;11">2. To provide information about the latest products or information;</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="11;11">We may use your Personal Data to provide notifications about new product releases, product development, retargeting, promotions, personalized offers, subscriptions, event participation, or information you may need. This information is not only limited to products / services from our services, both those that have been used and have never been used, but also products / services for our affiliates or partners that suit your needs. We may use your Personal Data and your transaction records to analyze your behavior and use it to provide information about our Services and / or products / services.</paragraph>

		<paragraph category="11;11">3. Analyze Customer behavior to provide better and more appropriate experience, services and information;</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="11;11">We use your Personal Data from your interactions with our services to analyze your interests and behavior patterns so that we can provide better experiences, services, promotions and information for your needs.</paragraph>

		<paragraph category="11;11">4. To inform you about the benefits, programs and opportunities that we provide to you;</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="11;11">We and / or Affiliates can communicate to you about the benefits, programs and opportunities that can be provided related to Our Services and / or Our Affiliates.</paragraph>

		<paragraph category="11;11">5. To get in touch with third parties / our partners;        </paragraph>
		<paragraph category="11,17.1,17.2,12;11,17.1,17.2,12">We can share your Personal Data (which has been encrypted and in anonymous format) with third parties / Our partners relating to our business interests and / or our affiliates and / or other needs including but not limited to the completion of transactions for our services and / or Our Affiliates who come into contact with Customers. We also share your Personal Data with third parties / our partners who we think can provide their content, products or services according to your interests. We ensure that our third parties / partners are chosen with care and are obliged to keep your Personal Data safe.</paragraph>

		<paragraph category="11,12;11,12">6. To protect our content and services;</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="11,12;11,12">We use Personal Data to prevent potential illegal activities and enforce the Terms of Use. We also use a variety of technological systems to detect unusual activity for abuse, such as spam, plagiarism, piracy and so on.</paragraph>

		<paragraph category="11;11">7. To get your suggestions and input from time to time;</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="11;11">We can ask the customer to provide suggestions, so that the product / service is more in line with what the customer needs and is interested in (for example through surveys, research on usage, group discussions). </paragraph>
	</segment>
	<segment>
		<title tagname="strong" depth="4" font-size="0.94" font-weight="1.75" category="8,9;8,9">THE DATA THAT WE COLLECT</title>
		<segment>
			<title tagname="p" depth="1" font-size="0.94" font-weight="1.0" category="8,9.1;8,9.1">1. We collect some Personal Data which is directly provided by you as follows:</title>
			<paragraph category="8,9.1;8,9.1">a. Name 
b. Contact information (phone, email) 
c. Date of birth 
d. Place of birth 
e. Demographics: gender, occupation, 
f. Personal identification information (KTP, SIM, Passport, and other personal identification) 
g. Emergency contact information 
h. Social media profile information 
i. Education and employment information 
j.  Information (s) that are of interest 
k. Other information from you, which is uploaded or provided to us. </paragraph>
		</segment>
		<segment>
			<title tagname="p" depth="1" font-size="0.94" font-weight="1.0" category="8,9.2;8,9.2">2.  We also collect some other information when you use our Portal and / or services, namely:</title>
			<paragraph category="8,9.2;8,9.2">a. Information about the device (s) you are using 
b. Information about service use 
c. Cookies. 
d. Authentication data 
e. Location information 
f. Data that has been recorded through one of the Affiliate's services will also be used to improve the Customer experience in all lines of our and Affiliate business. </paragraph>
			<paragraph category="8,9.2,11;8,9.2,11">3. Cookies referred to in letter c above are small text files that are sent to and stored on your computer, smartphone or other device to access the internet, whenever you use our Services through the Portal. Cookies are useful because they allow the Portal to recognize the user's device 

Cookies help us personalize the Portal and fulfill User interests and desires. We use cookies to protect your privacy. Our portal does not use cookies to collect personal information from your device. We never store passwords or similar sensitive data in cookies </paragraph>
			<paragraph category="8,9.2,11,17.1;8,9.2,11,17.1">We use 'analytics' cookies to help analyze how users access the Portal. By showing how and when users use the Portal, cookies help us find out which Portal pages are popular and which are not, and how we can improve the Portal for you. We use 'analytics' cookies on the Portal so that as such, we only share this cookie information with third parties / our partners, namely in an aggregate and anonymous format (overall) and there is no personal information. </paragraph>
			<paragraph category="4.6,11;4.6,11">How can you manage your cookies? The browsers of most computers, smartphones, and other web-enabled devices are usually set up to accept cookies. You have the option to control the acceptance of cookies yourself and, if you wish, you can block them completely by configuring your Internet browser. Please see the documentation for your browser to change your preferences regarding these cookies. 

Please note that cookies are used to activate and improve certain functions on the Portal. If you choose to disable certain cookies, this will likely affect how our Portal works. </paragraph>
		</segment>
	</segment>
	<segment>
		<title tagname="strong" depth="4" font-size="0.94" font-weight="1.75" category="19;19">
			THE DATA THAT WE DO NOT COLLECT</title>
			<paragraph category="19;19">We really appreciate the confidentiality of your data, therefore, we do not collect any data in the form of any content from photo albums, short message application communications (app messengers), and contact information /phonebook contained in your device. </paragraph>

	</segment>
	<segment>
		<title tagname="strong" depth="4" font-size="0.94" font-weight="1.75" category="12;12">
			SECURITY</title>
		<paragraph category="12,8,9,16.2;12,8,9,16.2">1.  Confidentiality of your information and Personal Data is a major concern for us. We make the best efforts and procedures to protect and guarantee Personal Data and we periodically conduct internal evaluations to increase security so that your Personal Data is safe from interference from unauthorized parties. We ensure that the Personal Data that we obtain is in the form of encrypted data both in the transmission process and in storage on the server. However, we cannot fully guarantee that our system cannot be penetrated by viruses, malware, and interference from unauthorized parties. </paragraph>
		<paragraph category="12;12">2. Users are responsible for always maintaining the confidentiality of information data contained in the Portal and in connection with the use of the Service, including but not limited to the confidentiality of the password that the User uses to access the account on the KG Media Portal. Please do not disclose and share your Personal Data, including your account password with anyone and keep your device safe. We are not responsible if you experience losses caused by your negligence in maintaining the confidentiality of information data in connection with the use of the Service and your account on the Portal, and you hereby release us, our directors, board of commissioners, employees, agents, and / or our affiliates. , from every claim, lawsuit, compensation, and / or claims that the User submits in connection with the unauthorized use and / or access to your account. </paragraph>
	</segment>
	<segment>
		<title tagname="strong" depth="4" font-size="0.94" font-weight="1.75" category="19;19">ADVERTISING</title>
		<paragraph category="8,9.2,11;8,9.2,11">1.  The advertisements that appear on the Portal may be sent to you by our partners, who may apply cookies. These cookies allow the server on each advertisement to recognize the User's device whenever they send an online advertisement to collect non-personal data about the User or other people who use the User's device. </paragraph>
 		<paragraph category="8,9.2,11;8,9.2,11">2. When you use our Portal, certain advertisements may appear which are products of our partners. Our partners, as third party vendors, use cookies to serve ads on our Portal </paragraph>
	</segment>
	<segment>
		<title tagname="strong" depth="4" font-size="0.94" font-weight="1.75" category="15;15">PROVISIONS ON CHILDREN UNDER AGE</title>
		<paragraph category="15;15">Each creation of a KG Media Portal account and its Affiliates is prohibited from being carried out by children under the age of 18 (eighteen) years or under the age determined by laws and regulation without consent from / not represent by their parent / guardian. We cannot distinguish directly about a person's age when creating the Portal account and / or using Our Services through the Portal. </paragraph>
		<paragraph category="15;15">Any use of the Service and / or creation of a Portal account that does have a segmentation for children must still be under the supervision and approval of their parents and / or guardians. </paragraph>
		<paragraph category="15,4.6;15,4.6">If there is an underage/child who has provided Personal Data without the consent of / not represent by the parent or guardian, the parent or guardian must contact KG Media (see Section O) to delete the relevant Personal Data and stop using the Portal account and / or the Service ( if the Service and / or Portal is not for the segmentation of children). </paragraph>
	</segment>
	<segment>
		<title tagname="strong" depth="4" font-size="0.94" font-weight="1.75" category="8;8">
			TECHNICAL AND REGULATORY INFORMATION</title>
		<paragraph category="8,9.2;8,9.2">1.  User personal data: We collect Personal Data from Users through various means, including but not limited to, when the User visits the Portal, uses features, accesses the content we provide on the Portal, when registering as a User, when the User uses the service and etc. Users can also be asked to provide data, among others, email address, home / office address, telephone number and other required information. </paragraph>
		<paragraph category="8,9.2;8,9.2">2.  User non-personal data: We may collect User non-personal data when they interact with the Portal and / or our services. Any non-personal data including but not limited tonames browser,types computer, telephone devices, or other information relating to how Users connect to our Portal, such as systems operating, internet services, social media, and other related information. </paragraph>
		<paragraph category="8,9.3;8,9.3">3.  In the event that when you choose to link your social media account or accounts related to other third party services to our Services and / or Portal, then you may ask a third party to send certain information to us from that social media account or service account. and you allow us to collect, store, and use what they send to us in accordance with what is described in this Privacy Policy.</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="19;19"> 4. Logging Practices; </paragraph>
		<paragraph category="8,9.2;8,9.2">We automatically record the Internet Protocol (IP) address of the User (web based application) and the session of the user (mobile application). We also record several materials to identify users of the Portal, including: </paragraph>
		<paragraph category="19;19">· Type / version of browser/ device </paragraph>
		<paragraph category="19;19">· The operating system used </paragraph>
		<paragraph category="19;19">· The date and time of the request server </paragraph>
		<paragraph category="19;19">· The location (latitude and longitude) </paragraph>
		<paragraph category="19;19">For mobile applications, we use the following ingredients to identify: </paragraph>
		<paragraph category="19;19">· Brand and / or type / version of the device </paragraph>
		<paragraph category="19;19">· Device IMEI </paragraph>
		<paragraph category="19;19">· The operating system used </paragraph>
		<paragraph category="19;19">· The date and time of the request server</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="19;19"> · The location (latitude and longitude) </paragraph>
		<paragraph category="19;19">· Other information provided by the operating system, browser or device </paragraph>
		<paragraph category="11;11">This identification is used on all of our services and portals to enable understanding of customer data from between products / services. This creates greater opportunities for us to provide better service to customers. </paragraph>
		<paragraph category="19;19">5. External links behavior: Some of our services / portals may contain links to other sites / applications created and managed by other parties / our partners. When you enter another site / application, please note that we are not responsible for the collection of data or content from the site / application and any information they may collect, even though our name or logo may appear on the site / the application. We ask you to be vigilant when leaving our Portal and reading the privacy terms of those other sites / applications that you visit, because the privacy policies of these other sites / applications may be different from ours </paragraph>
		<paragraph category="19;19">6. Do Not Track (DNT): is a self-regulatory initiative designed by the online advertising industry to provide options in the types of advertisements they may see and select from online behavioral ads provided by companies participating in this. We do not respond to DNT in your browser settings. </paragraph>
		<paragraph category="16.1,10;16.1,10">7. If you are no longer a registered user or use our services, we will keep Personal Data for at least 5 (five) years from the date you last became a registered user or since the last date you used our services / accessed the Portal, as required. based on the laws and regulations in force. </paragraph>
		<paragraph category="17.1,17.2;17.1,17.2">8. Responses to legal requests: We reserve the right to share your information in response to requests for your Personal Data information from Government authorities and / or agencies authorized or required by law. </paragraph>
	</segment>
	<segment>
		<title tagname="strong" depth="4" font-size="0.94" font-weight="1.75" category="4;4">
			PERSONAL DATA STATEMENT AND APPROVAL</title>
		<paragraph category="19;4">1.  By using our Portal and / or services, it means that you state that you have read, understood and agreed to this Privacy Policy and all changes that we have made from time to time and agree to allow us to use, implement, process, and transfer your Personal Data as stated in this Privacy Policy.</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="17.1,17.2,11;17.1,17.2,11"> 2.  You also acknowledge that you agree and agree to share all information that has been provided to us and give us the authority to delete, use and share your personal data with our affiliates and / or other third parties (such as our partners, vendors and others) to support our Services and / or Portal as well as our business activities and our Affiliates. </paragraph>
	</segment>
	<segment>
		<title tagname="strong" depth="4" font-size="0.94" font-weight="1.75" category="4.9,4.4;4.9,4.4">
			REMOVAL OF APPROVAL AND DELETION OF PERSONAL DATA</title>
		<paragraph category="4.2,4.3;4.2,4.3">1.  If you are a registered user, you can review, revise and correct your Personal Data through the User profile setting service on the Portal. </paragraph>
		<paragraph category="4.9,4.4;4.9,4.4">2.  You may withdraw your consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your Personal Data and / or delete your stored Personal Data by contacting us in the correspondence information described in section O below. </paragraph>
	</segment>
	<segment>
		<title tagname="strong" depth="4" font-size="0.94" font-weight="1.75" category="19;19">
			E-mail ADDRESS POLICY</title>
		<paragraph category="4.9;4.9">1.  If you wish to unsubscribe from receiving newsletters in your e-mails, please follow the unsubscribe or unsubscribe steps in the bottom corner of the respective Portal. </paragraph>
		<paragraph category="19;19">2.  We can send emails in the form of invitations to participate in user surveys, responses as visitors or users, as well as existing or developing services. </paragraph>
		<paragraph category="8,9.1,16;8,9.1,16">3.  If you communicate with us via email, we may retain and or store the contents of your e-mail messages, including a history of conversations between us and you and the e-mail address and information you provide during the communication. </paragraph>
		<paragraph category="19;19">4.  If you wish to send an e-mail to us, it is recommended that you understand that the information contained in the e-mail is not secure or encrypted, so that it may be seen by other parties. Thus, you are obliged to be careful when sending something that is confidential to our e-mail. In this case, we are not responsible for any email you send to us and there is no obligation for us to provide assistance for any events that harm you. </paragraph>

	</segment>
	<segment>
		<title tagname="strong" depth="4" font-size="0.94" font-weight="1.75" category="19;19">
			DISPUTE SETTLEMENT AND LANGUAGE</title>
		<paragraph category="19;19">1.  KG Media and User hereby agree to make every effort possible to reach a settlement by deliberation no later than 30 (thirty) working days since one of the parties receives a written letter from the other party. </paragraph>
		<paragraph category="19;19">2.  If the settlement through deliberation fails to reach a consensus within the stipulated time, then the dispute can be resolved by following the relevant laws and regulations. </paragraph>
		<paragraph category="19;19">3.  Language: In the event of inconsistency between the English version of this Privacy Policy and the Bahasa Indonesia version of this Privacy Policy, then the Bahasa Indonesia version shall prevail. </paragraph>
	</segment>
	<segment>
		<title tagname="strong" depth="4" font-size="0.94" font-weight="1.75" category="5;5">
			CHANGES TO THE PRIVACY POLICY</title>
		<paragraph category="5;5">KG Media may change this Privacy Policy from time to time by displaying the modified version on each and / or each Portal. You acknowledges and agrees that KG Media and/or its Affiliates reserve the right to change the Privacy Policy from time to time and You will check the Privacy Policy regularly for updates. By continuing to access the Portal and / or continuing the use of each KG Media Service, the Customer is deemed to have understood, submitted and agreed to this Privacy Policy and any changes thereof. </paragraph>
		<paragraph category="19;5">If a part of the Privacy Policy cannot be used / applicable, then that part does not affect the validity of other provisions. </paragraph>
	</segment>
	<segment>
		<title tagname="strong" depth="4" font-size="0.94" font-weight="1.75" category="1.2;1.2">
			CONTACT US</title>
		<paragraph category="1.2;1.2">If you have questions or interests regarding this Privacy Policy or regarding the use of Personal Data, contact us via: </paragraph>
		<paragraph category="1.2;1.2">Jl Palmerah Selatan No. 22-28, Tanah Abang, Jakarta, Indonesia 10270</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="1.2;1.2">Tel: 62-21 53699200</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="1.2;1.2">Fax: 62-21 53503777 </paragraph>

	</segment>
	<segment>
		<title tagname="strong" depth="4" font-size="0.94" font-weight="1.75" category="5;5">
			EFFECTIVE DATE AND MISCELLANEOUS</title>
		<paragraph category="5;5">This Privacy Policy was last updated and amended on February 22, 2020 By using our Portal and/or Services, you are deemed to agree to this Privacy Policy including but not limited to all its changes.</paragraph>
	</segment>
</policy>