<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<policy>
	<url>https://www.  .com</url>
	<update_time>20/ /</update_time>
	<download_time>2021/02/18</download_time>
	<paragraph category="">Last updated: June 30, 2020. To see prior version, click here Goodreads LLC (together with its affiliates, “Goodreads,” “we,” or “us”) knows that you care how information aboutyou is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. Goodreads LLC is a subsidiary of Amazon.com, Inc. (“Amazon”). The information we collect is subject to the Amazon Privacy Notice ,except as otherwise stated in this notice. By visiting or using Goodreads.com and related services (the “Service”),you are accepting the practices described in the Amazon Privacy Notice as supplemented by this notice(the “Privacy Notice”). Please note that, if you have an account on www.amazon.com, information gathered byGoodreads may be correlated with any personal information that Amazon.com has and used by Goodreads and Amazonto improve the services we offer </paragraph>
	<segment>
		<title tagname="h2" depth="1" font-size="1.38" font-weight="1.0" category="19;19">User Content and Messages</title>
		<paragraph category="4.4,12,17;4.4,12,17">The Service allows you to post User Content, as defined in our Terms of Use .Any User Content you post becomes available to the public via the Service. User Content includes, but is notlimited to, reviews, comments, and visual content. If you remove User Content, copies may remain viewable incached and archived pages or if other users have copied or stored your User Content. </paragraph>
		<paragraph category="">Goodreads takes reasonable measures to keep messages that you send to other Members through the Service privatebetween you and the recipient. However, even if you have deleted the message from your Goodreads inbox or outbox,copies of the message may remain viewable in cached and archived pages or if other users have copied or stored themessage. </paragraph>
	</segment>
	<segment>
		<title tagname="h2" depth="1" font-size="1.38" font-weight="1.0" category="19;19">E-mail</title>
		<paragraph category="4.1,4.3,4.9,8,9,11;4.1,4.3,4.9,8,9,11">By providing Goodreads your e-mail address you consent to us sending you Service-related notices, including anynotices required by law, in lieu of communication by postal mail. We may also use your e-mail address to send youother messages, such as newsletters, changes to features, notices of member-initiated content, or special offers(“Other Messages”). If you do not want to receive Other Messages, you may opt out by changing your e-mailpreference settings in the account settings section of Goodreads.com after you have signed in using yourpersonal password. Opting out may prevent you from receiving e-mail messages regarding updates, improvements, oroffers. You may not opt out of Service-related e-mails. </paragraph>
	</segment>
	<segment>
		<title tagname="h2" depth="1" font-size="1.38" font-weight="1.0" category="4.3;4.3">Privacy Settings</title>
		<paragraph category="4.3,4.4s;4.3,4.4">Your name is used when you invite another person to join Goodreads, or when you request to add another member toyour friends list. To the extent that you do not wish to have your name shared in this manner, you should notmake use of these services. You can modify, delete, and set your privacy setting for information you provide usany time in the account settings section of Goodreads.com after you have signed in using your personal password. </paragraph>
	</segment>
	<segment>
		<title tagname="h2" depth="1" font-size="1.38" font-weight="1.0" category="6;6">Your Choices About Your Information</title>
		<paragraph category="4.2,4.3,4.6,11;4.2,4.3,4.6,11">You may access or change your information and preferences at any time in the account settings section ofGoodreads.com once you have signed in with your personal password. For example, you can control which actions,if any, will appear on your update feed, whether to display your e-mail address, whether to display your lastname, and what sort of e-mail notifications you will receive from the Service. You may, of course, decline tosubmit personally identifiable information through Goodreads, in which case Goodreads may not be able to providecertain services to you. </paragraph>
	</segment>
	<segment>
		<title tagname="h2" depth="1" font-size="1.38" font-weight="1.0" category="18.1;18.1">Cookies and Other Identifiers</title>
		<paragraph category="18.1;18.1">To enable our systems to recognize your browser or device and to provide and improve the Service, we use cookiesand other identifiers. For more information about cookies and how we use them, please read our Cookies notice. </paragraph>
	</segment>
	<segment>
		<title tagname="h2" depth="1" font-size="1.38" font-weight="1.0" category="19;19">Advertising</title>
		<paragraph category="11;11">We use your personal information to display interest-based ads for features, products, and services that might be ofinterest to you. We do not use information that personally identifies you to display interest-based ads. To learnmore, please read our Interest Based Ads notice. </paragraph>
	</segment>
	<segment>
		<title tagname="h2" depth="1" font-size="1.38" font-weight="1.0" category="15;15">Children's Privacy</title>
		<paragraph category="1.2,4.4,15;10.2,4.4,15">Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important. For that reason, Goodreads does not knowinglycollect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register.If you are under 13, please do not send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address,telephone number, or e-mail address. No one under age 13 is allowed to provide any personal information to or onGoodreads. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 withoutverification of parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that wemight have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us . </paragraph>
	</segment>
	<segment>
		<title tagname="h2" depth="1" font-size="1.38" font-weight="1.0" category="18.2;18.2">California Consumer Privacy Act</title>
		<paragraph category="18.2;18.2">Click here to read additional disclosures required under the California Consumer Privacy Act. </paragraph>
	</segment>
	<segment>
		<title tagname="h2" depth="1" font-size="1.38" font-weight="1.0" category="5;5">Changes to Our Privacy Policy</title>
		<paragraph category="5;5">If we change this Privacy Notice, we will post those changes on our website to keep you aware of what information wecollect, how we use it and under what circumstances we may disclose it. Changes to this Privacy Notice are effectivewhen they are posted on this page. </paragraph>
		<paragraph category="1.2;1.2">If you have any questions about this Privacy Notice, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site,please contact us ,or send mail to: Goodreads, Inc 188 Spear Street,Suite 250 San Francisco,CA94105 </paragraph>
		<segment>
			<title tagname="h3" depth="1" font-size="0.88" font-weight="1.75" category="5;5">Updates</title>
			<paragraph category="5;5">June 30, 2020: We replaced our former privacy policy with a new one. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. October 16, 2008: We replaced our former privacy policy with a new one. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. </paragraph>
		</segment>
	</segment>
</policy>