<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<policy>
	<segment>
		<title tagname="h3" depth="1" font-size="3.0" font-weight="1.25" category="">
			What this Privacy Policy Covers
			</title>
		<paragraph category="">This Privacy Policy covers how we treat Personal Data that we gather when you access or use our Services. “Personal Data” means any information that identifies or relates to a particular individual and also includes information referred to as “personally identifiable information” or “personal information” under applicable data privacy laws, rules or regulations. This Privacy Policy does not cover the practices of companies we don’t own or control or people we don’t manage.</paragraph>
	</segment>
	<segment>
		<title tagname="h3" depth="1" font-size="3.0" font-weight="1.25" category="15;15">
			Personal Data of Children
			</title>
		<paragraph category="15;15">As noted in the Terms of Use, we do not knowingly collect or solicit Personal Data about children under 13 years of age; if you are a child under the age of 13, please do not attempt to register for or otherwise use the Services or send us any Personal Data. If we learn we have collected Personal Data from a child under 13 years of age, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that a child under 13 years of age may have provided Personal Data to us, please contact us at privacy@coursehero.com.</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="1.2,10.5,15;1.2,10.5,15">If you are under the age of 16 and a resident of the European Union (“EU”), United Kingdom, Lichtenstein, Norway or Iceland, please have your parent or guardian contact us at privacy@coursehero.com to provide consent before you attempt to register for or otherwise use the Services or send us any Personal Data.</paragraph>
	</segment>
	<segment>
		<title tagname="h3" depth="1" font-size="3.0" font-weight="1.25" category="19;19">Personal Data</title>
		<segment>
			<title tagname="h5" depth="1" font-size="2.25" font-weight="1.25" category="8.1,9;8.1,9">
				Categories of Personal Data We Collect
				</title>
			<paragraph category="8.1,9;8.1,9">This chart details the categories of Personal Data that we collect and have collected over the past 12 months:</paragraph>
		<item>First and last name</item>
		<item>Email</item>
		<item>Phone number</item>
		<item>Mailing Address</item>
		<item>Unique identifiers such as passwords</item>
		<item>Other unique personal or online identifiers including school identifiers</item>
		<item>Service Providers</item>
		<item>Advertising Partners</item>
		<item>Analytics Partners</item>
		<item>Business Partners</item>
		<item>Parties You Authorize, Access or Authenticate</item>
		<item>Payment card type</item>
		<item>Credit or debit card number (last 4 digits only)</item>
		<item>Credit or debit card number (full number)</item>
		<item>Billing zip code</item>
		<item>Service Providers</item>
		<item>Advertising Partners</item>
		<item>Analytics Partners</item>
		<item>IP address</item>
		<item>Device ID</item>
		<item>Type of device/operating system/browser used to access the Services</item>
		<item>Service Providers</item>
		<item>Advertising Partners</item>
		<item>Analytics Partners</item>
		<item>Parties You Authorize, Access or Authenticate</item>
		<item>Browsing or search history</item>
		<item>Web page interactions</item>
		<item>Referring webpage/source through which you accessed the Services</item>
		<item>Non-identifiable request IDs</item>
		<item>Statistics associated with the interaction between device or browser and the Services</item>
		<item>Service Providers</item>
		<item>Advertising Partners</item>
		<item>Analytics Partners</item>
		<item>Service Providers</item>
		<item>Advertising Partners</item>
		<item>Analytics Partners</item>
		<item>Business Partners</item>
		<item>Parties You Authorize, Access or Authenticate</item>
		<item>Job title</item>
		<item>Job history</item>
		<item>Service Providers</item>
		<item>Analytics Partners</item>
		<item>Parties You Authorize, Access or Authenticate</item>
		<item>Grades or transcripts</item>
		<item>Student financial information</item>
		<item>Service Providers</item>
		<item>Analytics Partners</item>
	</segment>
		<segment>
			<title tagname="h5" depth="1" font-size="2.25" font-weight="1.25" category="8,9;8,9">
				Categories of Sources of Personal Data
				</title>
			<segment>
				<title tagname="h6" depth="3" font-size="2.25" font-weight="1.25" category="8,9.1,8,9.2;8,9.1,8,9.2">
					You
					</title>
				<item>
When you provide such information directly to us.

When you create an account or use our interactive tools and Services.
When you voluntarily provide information in free-form text boxes through the Services or through responses to surveys or questionnaires.
When you send us an email or otherwise contact us.

</item>
		<item>When you create an account or use our interactive tools and Services.</item>
		<item>When you voluntarily provide information in free-form text boxes through the Services or through responses to surveys or questionnaires.</item>
		<item>When you send us an email or otherwise contact us.</item>
		<item>
When you use the Services and such information is collected automatically.

Through Cookies (defined in the “Tracking Tools, Advertising and Opt-Out” section below).
If you download our mobile application or use a location-enabled browser, we may receive information about your location and mobile device, as applicable.
If you download and install certain applications and software we make available, we may receive and collect information transmitted from your device for the purpose of providing you the relevant Services, such as information regarding when you are logged on and available to receive updates or alert notices.

</item>
		<item>Through Cookies (defined in the “Tracking Tools, Advertising and Opt-Out” section below).</item>
		<item>If you download our mobile application or use a location-enabled browser, we may receive information about your location and mobile device, as applicable.</item>
		<item>If you download and install certain applications and software we make available, we may receive and collect information transmitted from your device for the purpose of providing you the relevant Services, such as information regarding when you are logged on and available to receive updates or alert notices.</item>
	</segment>
			<segment>
				<title tagname="h6" depth="3" font-size="2.25" font-weight="1.25" category="8,9.3;8,9.3">
					Third Parties
					</title>
				<item>
Vendors

We may use analytics providers to analyze how you interact and engage with the Services, or third parties may help us provide you with customer support.
We may use vendors to obtain information to generate leads and create user profiles.

</item>
		<item>We may use analytics providers to analyze how you interact and engage with the Services, or third parties may help us provide you with customer support.</item>
		<item>We may use vendors to obtain information to generate leads and create user profiles.</item>
		<item>
Advertising Partners
We receive information about you from some of our vendors who assist us with marketing or promotional services related to how you interact with our websites, applications, products, Services, advertisements or communications.
</item>
		<item>
Social Networks
If you provide your social network account credentials to us or otherwise sign in to the Services through a third-party site or service, some content and/or information in those accounts may be transmitted into your account with us.
</item>
	</segment>
			<paragraph category="8,9;8,9">We collect Personal Data about you from the following categories of sources:</paragraph>
	</segment>
		<segment>
			<title tagname="h5" depth="1" font-size="2.25" font-weight="1.25" category="11;11">
				Our Commercial or Business Purposes for Collecting Personal Data
			</title>
			<segment>
				<title tagname="h6" depth="3" font-size="2.25" font-weight="1.25" category="11;11">
					Providing, Customizing and Improving the Services
					</title>
				<item>Creating and managing your account or other user profiles.</item>
		<item>Processing orders or other transactions; billing.</item>
		<item>Providing you with the products, services or information you request.</item>
		<item>Meeting or fulfilling the reason you provided the information to us.</item>
		<item>Providing support and assistance for the Services.</item>
		<item>Improving the Services, including testing, research, internal analytics and product development.</item>
		<item>Personalizing the Services, website content and communications based on your preferences.</item>
		<item>Doing fraud protection, security and debugging.</item>
		<item>Carrying out other business purposes stated when collecting your Personal Data or as otherwise set forth in applicable data privacy laws, such as the California Consumer Privacy Act (the “CCPA”).</item>
	</segment>
			<segment>
				<title tagname="h6" depth="3" font-size="2.25" font-weight="1.25" category="11;11">
					Marketing the Services
					</title>
				<item>Marketing and selling the Services.</item>
		<item>Showing you advertisements, including interest-based or online behavioral advertising.</item>
	</segment>
			<segment>
				<title tagname="h6" depth="3" font-size="2.25" font-weight="1.25" category="11;11">
					Corresponding with You
					</title>
				<item>Responding to correspondence that we receive from you, contacting you when necessary or requested, and sending you information about Course Hero or the Services.</item>
		<item>Sending emails and other communications according to your preferences or that display content that we think will interest you.</item>
	</segment>
			<segment>
				<title tagname="h6" depth="3" font-size="2.25" font-weight="1.25" category="10.6,11;10.6,11">
					Meeting Legal Requirements and Enforcing Legal Terms
					</title>
				<item>Fulfilling our legal obligations under applicable law, regulation, court order or other legal process, such as preventing, detecting and investigating security incidents and potentially illegal or prohibited activities.</item>
		<item>Protecting the rights, property or safety of you, Course Hero or another party.</item>
		<item>Enforcing any agreements with you.</item>
		<item>Responding to claims that any posting or other content violates third-party rights.</item>
		<item>Resolving disputes.</item>
		<paragraph category="4.1,8,9,11;4.1,8,9,11">We will not collect additional categories of Personal Data or use the Personal Data we collected for materially different, unrelated or incompatible purposes without providing you notice.</paragraph>
	</segment>
		</segment>
	</segment>
	<segment>
		<title tagname="h3" depth="1" font-size="3.0" font-weight="1.25" category="17;17">
			How We Share Your Personal Data
			</title>
		<segment>
			<title tagname="strong" depth="3" font-size="1.88" font-weight="1.75" category="19;17.1">
				Service Providers.
				</title>
			<item>Hosting, technology and communication providers.</item>
		<item>Security and fraud prevention consultants.</item>
		<item>Analytics providers.</item>
		<item>Support and customer service vendors.</item>
		<item>Payment processors.</item>
		<item>Our payment processing partners Braintree and PayPal collect your voluntarily-provided payment card information necessary to process your payment.</item>
		<item>Please see Braintree’s and PayPal’s terms of service and privacy policy for information on each of their use and storage of your Personal Data.</item>
	</segment>
		<segment>
			<title tagname="strong" depth="3" font-size="1.88" font-weight="1.75" category="19;17.1">
				Advertising Partners.
				</title>
			<item>Ad networks.</item>
		<item>Data brokers.</item>
		<item>Marketing providers.</item>
	</segment>
		<segment>
			<title tagname="strong" depth="3" font-size="1.88" font-weight="1.75" category="19;17.1">
				Business Partners.
				</title>
			<item>Businesses that you have a relationship with.</item>
		<item>Companies that we partner with to offer joint promotional offers or opportunities.</item>
	</segment>
		<segment>
			<title tagname="strong" depth="3" font-size="1.88" font-weight="1.75" category="">Parties You Authorize, Access or Authenticate</title>
					<item>Social media services.</item>
		</segment>
		<segment>
			<title tagname="h5" depth="1" font-size="2.25" font-weight="1.25" category="10.6;10.6,17.2">
				Legal Obligations
				</title>
			<paragraph category="10.6,17.1,17.2;10.6,17.1,17.2">We may share any Personal Data that we collect with third parties in conjunction with any of the activities set forth under “Meeting Legal Requirements and Enforcing Legal Terms” in the “Our Commercial or Business Purposes for Collecting Personal Data” section above.</paragraph>
	</segment>
		<segment>
			<title tagname="h5" depth="1" font-size="2.25" font-weight="1.25" category="19;17.2">
				Business Transfers
				</title>
			<paragraph category="17.1,17.2;17.1,17.2">All of your Personal Data that we collect may be transferred to a third party if we undergo a merger, acquisition, bankruptcy or other transaction in which that third party assumes control of our business (in whole or in part). Should one of these events occur, we will make reasonable efforts to notify you before your information becomes subject to different privacy and security policies and practices.</paragraph>
	</segment>
		<segment>
			<title tagname="h5" depth="1" font-size="2.25" font-weight="1.25" category="19;17.2">
				Data that is Not Personal Data
				</title>
			<paragraph category="17.1,17.2;17.1,17.2">We may create aggregated, de-identified or anonymized data from the Personal Data we collect, including by removing information that makes the data personally identifiable to a particular user. We may use such aggregated, de-identified or anonymized data and share it with third parties for our lawful business purposes, including to analyze, build and improve the Services and promote our business, provided that we will not share such data in a manner that could identify you.</paragraph>
	</segment>
		<paragraph category="10,17.1;10,17.1">We disclose your Personal Data to the categories of service providers and other parties listed in this section. Depending on state laws that may be applicable to you, some of these disclosures may constitute a “sale” of your Personal Data. For more information, please refer to the state-specific sections below.</paragraph>
	</segment>
	<segment>
		<title tagname="h3" depth="1" font-size="3.0" font-weight="1.25" category="19;19">
			Tracking Tools, Advertising and Opt-Out
			</title>
		<segment>
			<title tagname="strong" depth="3" font-size="1.88" font-weight="1.75" category="18.1;18.1">
				Essential Cookies.
				</title>
			<item>Essential Cookies are required for providing you with features or services that you have requested. For example, certain Cookies enable you to log into secure areas of our Services. Disabling these Cookies may make certain features and services unavailable.</item>
	</segment>
		<segment>
			<title tagname="strong" depth="3" font-size="1.88" font-weight="1.75" category="18.1;18.1">
				Functional Cookies.
				</title>
			<item>Functional Cookies are used to record your choices and settings regarding our Services, maintain your preferences over time and recognize you when you return to our Services. These Cookies help us to personalize our content for you, greet you by name and remember your preferences (for example, your choice of language or region).</item>
	</segment>
		<segment>
			<title tagname="strong" depth="3" font-size="1.88" font-weight="1.75" category="18.1;18.1">
				Performance/Analytical Cookies.
				</title>
			<item>Performance/Analytical Cookies allow us to understand how visitors use our Services. They do this by collecting information about the number of visitors to the Services, what pages visitors view on our Services and how long visitors are viewing pages on the Services. Performance/Analytical Cookies also help us measure the performance of our advertising campaigns in order to help us improve our campaigns and the Services’ content for those who engage with our advertising. For example, Google Inc. (“Google”) uses cookies in connection with its Google Analytics services. Google’s ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to the Services is subject to the Google Analytics Terms of Use and the Google Privacy Policy. You have the option to opt-out of Google’s use of Cookies by visiting the Google advertising opt-out page at www.google.com/privacy_ads.html or the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on at https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/.</item>
	</segment>
		<segment>
			<title tagname="strong" depth="3" font-size="1.88" font-weight="1.75" category="18.1;18.1">
				Retargeting/Advertising Cookies.
				</title>
			<item>Retargeting/Advertising Cookies collect data about your online activity and identify your interests so that we can provide advertising that we believe is relevant to you. For more information about this, please see the section below titled “Information about Interest-Based Advertisements.”</item>
		<paragraph category="18.1;18.1">You can decide whether or not to accept Cookies through your internet browser’s settings. Most browsers have an option for turning off the Cookie feature, which will prevent your browser from accepting new Cookies, as well as (depending on the sophistication of your browser software) allow you to decide on acceptance of each new Cookie in a variety of ways. You can also delete all Cookies that are already on your device. If you do this, however, you may have to manually adjust some preferences every time you visit our website and some of the Services and functionalities may not work.</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="18.1;18.1">To explore what Cookie settings are available to you, look in the “preferences” or “options” section of your browser’s menu. To find out more information about Cookies, including information about how to manage and delete Cookies, please visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org/ or https://ico.org.uk/for-the-public/online/cookies/ if you are located in the European Union.</paragraph>
	</segment>
		<segment>
			<title tagname="h5" depth="1" font-size="2.25" font-weight="1.25" category="19;19">
				Information about Interest-Based Advertisements:
				</title>
			<paragraph category="8,9,11;8,9,11">We may serve advertisements, and also allow third-party ad networks, including third-party ad servers, ad agencies, ad technology vendors and research firms, to serve advertisements through the Services. These advertisements may be targeted to users who fit certain general profile categories or display certain preferences or behaviors (“Interest-Based Ads”). Information for Interest-Based Ads (including Personal Data) may be provided to us by you, or derived from the usage patterns of particular users on the Services and/or services of third parties. Such information may be gathered through tracking users’ activities across time and unaffiliated properties, including when you leave the Services. To accomplish this, we or our service providers may deliver Cookies, including a file (known as a “web beacon”) from an ad network to you through the Services. Web beacons allow ad networks to provide anonymized, aggregated auditing, research and reporting for us and for advertisers. Web beacons also enable ad networks to serve targeted advertisements to you when you visit other websites. Web beacons allow ad networks to view, edit or set their own Cookies on your browser, just as if you had requested a web page from their site.</paragraph>
	</segment>
		<paragraph category="18.1;18.1">The Services use cookies and similar technologies such as pixel tags, web beacons, clear GIFs and JavaScript (collectively, “Cookies”) to enable our servers to recognize your web browser, tell us how and when you visit and use our Services, analyze trends, learn about our user base and operate and improve our Services. Cookies are small pieces of data– usually text files – placed on your computer, tablet, phone or similar device when you use that device to access our Services. We may also supplement the information we collect from you with information received from third parties, including third parties that have placed their own Cookies on your device(s). Please note that because of our use of Cookies, the Services do not support “Do Not Track” requests sent from a browser at this time.</paragraph>
		<item>Essential Cookies. Essential Cookies are required for providing you with features or services that you have requested. For example, certain Cookies enable you to log into secure areas of our Services. Disabling these Cookies may make certain features and services unavailable.</item>
	</segment>
	<segment>
		<title tagname="h3" depth="1" font-size="3.0" font-weight="1.25" category="12,16;12,16">
			Data Security and Retention
			</title>
		<paragraph category="12,16;12,16">We seek to protect your Personal Data from unauthorized access, use and disclosure using appropriate physical, technical, organizational and administrative security measures based on the type of Personal Data and how we are processing that data. You should also help protect your data by appropriately selecting and protecting your password and/or other sign-on mechanism; limiting access to your computer or device and browser; and signing off after you have finished accessing your account. Although we work to protect the security of your account and other data that we hold in our records, please be aware that no method of transmitting data over the internet or storing data is completely secure.</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="10.6,16.1;10.6,16.1">We retain Personal Data about you for as long as you have an open account with us or as otherwise necessary to provide you with our Services. In some cases we retain Personal Data for longer, if doing so is necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes or collect fees owed, or is otherwise permitted or required by applicable law, rule or regulation. We may further retain information in an anonymous or aggregated form where that information would not identify you personally.</paragraph>
	</segment>
	<segment>
		<title tagname="h3" depth="1" font-size="3.0" font-weight="1.25" category="18.2;18.2">
			California Resident Rights
			</title>
		<segment>
			<title tagname="h5" depth="1" font-size="2.25" font-weight="1.25" category="4.2;18.2">
				Access
				</title>
			<paragraph category="4.2;18.2">You have the right to request certain information about our collection and use of your Personal Data over the past 12 months. In response, we will provide you with the following information:</paragraph>
		<item>The categories of Personal Data that we have collected about you.</item>
		<item>The categories of sources from which that Personal Data was collected.</item>
		<item>The business or commercial purpose for collecting or selling your Personal Data.</item>
		<item>The categories of third parties with whom we have shared your Personal Data.</item>
		<item>The specific pieces of Personal Data that we have collected about you.</item>
		<paragraph category="17;18.2">If we have disclosed your Personal Data to any third parties for a business purpose over the past 12 months, we will identify the categories of Personal Data shared with each category of third party recipient. If we have sold your Personal Data over the past 12 months, we will identify the categories of Personal Data sold to each category of third party recipient.</paragraph>
	</segment>
		<segment>
			<title tagname="h5" depth="1" font-size="2.25" font-weight="1.25" category="4.4;18.2">
				Deletion
				</title>
			<paragraph category="4.4;18.2">You have the right to request that we delete the Personal Data that we have collected about you. Under the CCPA, this right is subject to certain exceptions: for example, we may need to retain your Personal Data to provide you with the Services or complete a transaction or other action you have requested. If your deletion request is subject to one of these exceptions, we may deny your deletion request.</paragraph>
	</segment>
		<segment>
			<title tagname="h5" depth="1" font-size="2.25" font-weight="1.25" category="4;18.2">
				Exercising Your Rights
				</title>
			<paragraph category="4;18.2">To exercise the rights described above, you or your Authorized Agent (defined below) must send us a request that (1) provides sufficient information to allow us to verify that you are the person about whom we have collected Personal Data, and (2) describes your request in sufficient detail to allow us to understand, evaluate and respond to it. Each request that meets both of these criteria will be considered a “Valid Request.” We may not respond to requests that do not meet these criteria. We will only use Personal Data provided in a Valid Request to verify your identity and complete your request. You do not need an account to submit a Valid Request.</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="4;18.2">We will work to respond to your Valid Request within 45 days of receipt. We will not charge you a fee for making a Valid Request unless your Valid Request(s) is excessive, repetitive or manifestly unfounded. If we determine that your Valid Request warrants a fee, we will notify you of the fee and explain that decision before completing your request.</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="4;18.2">You may submit a Valid Request using the following methods:</paragraph>
		<item>Call us at: 866-634-9397</item>
		<item>Email us at: privacy@coursehero.com</item>
		<item>Submit a form at this address: https://www.coursehero.com/takedown-notice/#/privacy-infringement</item>
		<paragraph category="4;18.2">You may also authorize an agent (an “Authorized Agent”) to exercise your rights on your behalf. To do this, you must provide your Authorized Agent with written permission to exercise your rights on your behalf, and we may request a copy of this written permission from your Authorized Agent when they make a request on your behalf.</paragraph>
	</segment>
		<segment>
			<title tagname="h5" depth="1" font-size="2.25" font-weight="1.25" category="4.9;18.2">
				Personal Data Sales Opt-Out and Opt-In
				</title>
			<paragraph category="19;18.2">We will not sell your Personal Data, and have not done so over the last 12 months.</paragraph>
	</segment>
		<segment>
			<title tagname="h5" depth="1" font-size="2.25" font-weight="1.25" category="4;18.2">
				We Will Not Discriminate Against You for Exercising Your Rights Under the CCPA
				</title>
			<paragraph category="4;18.2">We will not discriminate against you for exercising your rights under the CCPA. We will not deny you our goods or services, charge you different prices or rates, or provide you a lower quality of goods and services if you exercise your rights under the CCPA. However, we may offer different tiers of our Services as allowed by applicable data privacy laws (including the CCPA) with varying prices, rates or levels of quality of the goods or services you receive related to the value of Personal Data that we receive from you.</paragraph>
	</segment>
		<paragraph category="18.2;18.2">If you are a California resident, you have the rights set forth in this section. Please see the “Exercising Your Rights” section below for instructions regarding how to exercise these rights. Please note that we may process Personal Data of our customers’ end users or employees in connection with our provision of certain services to our customers. If we are processing your Personal Data as a service provider, you should contact the entity that collected your Personal Data in the first instance to address your rights with respect to such data.</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="18.2;18.2">If there are any conflicts between this section and any other provision of this Privacy Policy and you are a California resident, the portion that is more protective of Personal Data shall control to the extent of such conflict. If you have any questions about this section or whether any of the following rights apply to you, please contact us at privacy@coursehero.com.</paragraph>
	</segment>
	<segment>
		<title tagname="h3" depth="1" font-size="3.0" font-weight="1.25" category="19;19">Other State Law Privacy Rights</title>
		<segment>
			<title tagname="h5" depth="1" font-size="2.25" font-weight="1.25" category="18.2;18.2">
				California Resident Rights
				</title>
			<paragraph category="18.2;18.2">Under California Civil Code Sections 1798.83-1798.84, California residents are entitled to contact us to prevent disclosure of Personal Data to third parties for such third parties’ direct marketing purposes; in order to submit such a request, please contact us at privacy@coursehero.com.</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="18.2;18.2">Your browser may offer you a “Do Not Track” option, which allows you to signal to operators of websites and web applications and services that you do not wish such operators to track certain of your online activities over time and across different websites. Our Services do not support Do Not Track requests at this time. To find out more about “Do Not Track,” you can visit www.allaboutdnt.com.</paragraph>
	</segment>
		<segment>
			<title tagname="h5" depth="1" font-size="2.25" font-weight="1.25" category="18.2;18.2">
				Nevada Resident Rights
				</title>
			<paragraph category="18.2;18.2">If you are a resident of Nevada, you have the right to opt-out of the sale of certain Personal Data to third parties who intend to license or sell that Personal Data. You can exercise this right by contacting us at privacy@coursehero.com with the subject line “Nevada Do Not Sell Request” and providing us with your name and the email address associated with your account. Please note that we do not currently sell your Personal Data as sales are defined in Nevada Revised Statutes Chapter 603A.</paragraph>
	</segment>
	</segment>
	<segment>
		<title tagname="h3" depth="1" font-size="3.0" font-weight="1.25" category="4;4">European Union Data Subject Rights</title>
		<segment>
			<title tagname="h5" depth="1" font-size="2.25" font-weight="1.25" category="19;4">
				EU Residents
				</title>
			<paragraph category="4;4">If you are a resident of the European Union (“EU”), United Kingdom, Lichtenstein, Norway or Iceland, you may have additional rights under the EU General Data Protection Regulation (the “GDPR”) with respect to your Personal Data, as outlined below.</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="1.1;1.1">For this section, we use the terms “Personal Data” and “processing” as they are defined in the GDPR, but “Personal Data” generally means information that can be used to individually identify a person, and “processing” generally covers actions that can be performed in connection with data such as collection, use, storage and disclosure. Course Hero will be the controller of your Personal Data processed in connection with the Services.</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="1.2;1.2">If there are any conflicts between this this section and any other provision of this Privacy Policy, the policy or portion that is more protective of Personal Data shall control to the extent of such conflict. If you have any questions about this section or whether any of the following applies to you, please contact us at privacy@coursehero.com.</paragraph>
	</segment>
		<segment>
			<title tagname="h5" depth="1" font-size="2.25" font-weight="1.25" category="8,9;8,9">
				Personal Data We Collect
				</title>
			<paragraph category="8.1,9;8.1,9">The “Categories of Personal Data We Collect” section above details the Personal Data that we collect from you.</paragraph>
	</segment>
		<segment>
			<title tagname="h5" depth="1" font-size="2.25" font-weight="1.25" category="11,10;11,10">
				Personal Data Use and Processing Grounds
				</title>
			<segment>
				<title tagname="strong" depth="3" font-size="1.88" font-weight="1.75" category="10.1;10.1">
					Contractual Necessity:
					</title>
				<item> We process Personal Data as a matter of “contractual necessity”, meaning that we need to process the data to perform under our Terms of Use with you, which enables us to provide you with the Website. When we process data due to contractual necessity, failure to provide such Personal Data will result in your inability to use some or all portions of the Website that require such data.</item>
	</segment>
			<segment>
				<title tagname="strong" depth="3" font-size="1.88" font-weight="1.75" category="10.3;10.3">
					Legitimate Interest:
					</title>
				<item>Operation and improvement of our business, products and services</item>
		<item>Marketing of our products and services</item>
		<item>Provision of customer support</item>
		<item>Protection from fraud or security threats</item>
		<item>Compliance with legal obligations</item>
		<item>Completion of corporate transactions</item>
	</segment>
			<segment>
				<title tagname="strong" depth="3" font-size="1.88" font-weight="1.75" category="10.5;10.5">
					Consent:
					</title>
				<item>In some cases, we process Personal Data based on the consent you expressly grant to us at the time we collect such data. When we process Personal Data based on your consent, it will be expressly indicated to you at the point and time of collection.</item>
	</segment>
			<segment>
				<title tagname="strong" depth="3" font-size="1.88" font-weight="1.75" category="10.4;10.4">Other Processing Grounds:</title>
						<item> From time to time we may also need to process Personal Data to comply with a legal obligation, if it is necessary to protect the vital interests of you or other data subjects, or if it is necessary for a task carried out in the public interest.</item>
			</segment>
			<paragraph category="11;11">The “Our Commercial or Business Purposes for Collecting Personal Data” section above explains how we use your Personal Data.</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="10.1,10.3,10.5;10.1,10.3,10.5">We will only process your Personal Data if we have a lawful basis for doing so. Lawful bases for processing include consent, contractual necessity and our “legitimate interests” or the legitimate interest of others, as further described below.</paragraph>
	</segment>
		<segment>
			<title tagname="h5" depth="1" font-size="2.25" font-weight="1.25" category="17;17">
				Sharing Personal Data
				</title>
			<paragraph category="17;17">The “How We Share Your Personal Data” section above details how we share your Personal Data with third parties.</paragraph>
	</segment>
		<segment>
			<title tagname="h5" depth="1" font-size="2.25" font-weight="1.25" category="4;4">
				EU Data Subject Rights
				</title>
			<segment>
				<title tagname="strong" depth="3" font-size="1.88" font-weight="1.75" category="4.2;4.2">
					Access:
					</title>
				<item>Access: You can request more information about the Personal Data we hold about you and request a copy of such Personal Data. You can also access certain of your Personal Data by contacting us at privacy@coursehero.com.</item>
	</segment>
			<segment>
				<title tagname="strong" depth="3" font-size="1.88" font-weight="1.75" category="4.3;4.3">
					Rectification:
					</title>
				<item>Rectification: If you believe that any Personal Data we are holding about you is incorrect or incomplete, you can request that we correct or supplement such data. You can also correct some of this information directly by logging on to your account or by contacting us at privacy@coursehero.com.</item>
	</segment>
			<segment>
				<title tagname="strong" depth="3" font-size="1.88" font-weight="1.75" category="4.4;4.4">
					Erasure:
					</title>
				<item>Erasure: You can request that we erase some or all of your Personal Data from our systems.</item>
	</segment>
			<segment>
				<title tagname="strong" depth="3" font-size="1.88" font-weight="1.75" category="4.9;4.9">
					Withdrawal of Consent:
					</title>
				<item>Withdrawal of Consent: If we are processing your Personal Data based on your consent (as indicated at the time of collection of such data), you have the right to withdraw your consent at any time. Please note, however, that if you exercise this right, you may have to then provide express consent on a case-by-case basis for the use or disclosure of certain of your Personal Data, if such use or disclosure is necessary to enable you to utilize some or all of our Services.</item>
	</segment>
			<segment>
				<title tagname="strong" depth="3" font-size="1.88" font-weight="1.75" category="4.7;4.7">
					Portability:
					</title>
				<item>Portability: You can ask for a copy of your Personal Data in a machine-readable format. You can also request that we transmit the data to another controller where technically feasible.</item>
	</segment>
			<segment>
				<title tagname="strong" depth="3" font-size="1.88" font-weight="1.75" category="4.6;4.6">
					Objection:
					</title>
				<item>Objection: You can contact us to let us know that you object to the further use or disclosure of your Personal Data for certain purposes, such as for direct marketing purposes.</item>
	</segment>
			<segment>
				<title tagname="strong" depth="3" font-size="1.88" font-weight="1.75" category="4.5;4.5">
					Restriction of Processing:
					</title>
				<item>Restriction of Processing: You can ask us to restrict further processing of your Personal Data.</item>
	</segment>
			<segment>
				<title tagname="strong" depth="3" font-size="1.88" font-weight="1.75" category="7;7">Right to File Complaint:</title>
						<item>Right to File Complaint: You have the right to lodge a complaint about Course Hero’s practices with respect to your Personal Data with the supervisory authority of your country or EU Member State. A list of Supervisory Authorities is available here: https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members_en.</item>
			</segment>
			<paragraph category="4;4">You have certain rights with respect to your Personal Data, including those set forth below. For more information about these rights, or to submit a request, please email us at privacy@coursehero.com. Please note that in some circumstances, we may not be able to fully comply with your request, such as if it is frivolous or extremely impractical, if it jeopardizes the rights of others, or if it is not required by law, but in those circumstances, we will still respond to notify you of such a decision. In some cases, we may also need you to provide us with additional information, which may include Personal Data, if necessary to verify your identity and the nature of your request.</paragraph>
	</segment>
		<segment>
			<title tagname="h5" depth="1" font-size="2.25" font-weight="1.25" category="14;14">
				Transfers of Personal Data
				</title>
			<paragraph category="14.2;14.2">The Services are hosted and operated in the United States (“U.S.”) through Course Hero and its service providers, and if you do not reside in the U.S., laws in the U.S. may differ from the laws where you reside. By using the Services, you acknowledge that any Personal Data about you, regardless of whether provided by you or obtained from a third party, is being provided to Course Hero in the U.S. and will be hosted on U.S. servers, and you authorize Course Hero to transfer, store and process your information to and in the U.S., and possibly other countries. You hereby consent to the transfer of your data to the U.S. pursuant to the EU-U.S. or Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Frameworks, respectively, the details of which are further set forth below.</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="14.2;14.2">Course Hero has certified to the EU-U.S. and Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Frameworks set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection and use of Personal Data transferred from the EU and Switzerland to the U.S., respectively. For more information about the Privacy Shield Program, and to view Course Hero’s certification, please visit www.privacyshield.gov. Course Hero is committed to the Privacy Shield Principles of (1) notice, (2) consent, (3) accountability for onward transfer, (4) security, (5) data integrity and purpose limitation, (6) access and (7) recourse, enforcement and liability with respect to all Personal Data received from within the EU and Switzerland in reliance on the Privacy Shield. The Privacy Shield Principles require that we remain potentially liable if any third party processing Personal Data on our behalf fails to comply with these Privacy Shield Principles (except to the extent we are not responsible for the event giving rise to any alleged damage). Course Hero’s compliance with the Privacy Shield is subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission.</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="1.2;1.2">Please contact us at privacy@coursehero.com with any questions or concerns relating to our Privacy Shield Certification.</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="1.2;1.2">If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our U.S.-based third party dispute resolution provider (free of charge) at https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request. Under certain conditions, you may also be entitled to invoke binding arbitration for complaints not resolved by other means.</paragraph>
	</segment>
	</segment>
	<segment>
		<title tagname="h3" depth="1" font-size="3.0" font-weight="1.25" category="5;5">
			Changes to this Privacy Policy
			</title>
		<paragraph category="4.1,5;4.1,5">We’re constantly trying to improve our Services, so we may need to change this Privacy Policy from time to time, but we will alert you to any such changes by placing a notice on the Course Hero website, by sending you an email and/or by some other means. Please note that if you’ve opted not to receive legal notice emails from us (or you haven’t provided us with your email address), those legal notices will still govern your use of the Services, and you are still responsible for reading and understanding them. If you use the Services after any changes to the Privacy Policy have been posted, that means you agree to all of the changes. Use of information we collect is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is collected.</paragraph>
	</segment>
	<segment>
		<title tagname="h3" depth="1" font-size="3.0" font-weight="1.25" category="1.2;1.2">
			Contact Information:
			</title>
		<paragraph category="1.2;1.2">If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, the ways in which we collect and use your Personal Data or your choices and rights regarding such collection and use, please do not hesitate to contact us at:</paragraph>
		<paragraph category="2.2;2.2">Individuals in the EU may contact our EU representative according to Art. 27 GDPR regarding all requests related to data protection and privacy:</paragraph>
	</segment>
</policy>